✔ the half cent rounds up, not down — $0.70 at 5% is $0.04 (1.7309ms)
✔ the cents agree with data.js gstOn at every whole cent under $5,000 (1964.3075ms)
✔ an exempt client is charged nothing, and the total is the subtotal (2.1806ms)
✔ a rate the row does not carry is the ordinary 5%, never exempt (0.3699ms)
✔ a client rate that is neither camel nor snake case is still read (0.3578ms)
✔ null money is three blank cells, not a row of zeros (0.3213ms)
✔ commas, quotes and newlines in a label reach the CSV helper unaltered (0.9594ms)
✔ the ticket export carries the invoice number and the day it was invoiced (0.4305ms)
✔ a database with no invoice_number column says so instead of leaving a silent blank (0.5182ms)
✔ a client id the row does not carry is blank, never invented (0.5646ms)
✔ lines come out in the export's ticket order, each ticket's own order kept (0.5408ms)
✔ a line's total is quantity times rate, rounded the way the invoice rounds it (0.3056ms)
✔ a ticket with no lines is left out of the line export and counted out of it (0.3299ms)
✔ the line export says in the file that it carries no GST (0.213ms)
✔ an empty export is still a file with its caption and columns (0.1782ms)
✔ clearSessionState is declared above the recheck effect that captures it (1.4545ms)
✔ every early return in App comes after the last hook call (0.853ms)
✔ runs every item in order, one at a time (4.6474ms)
✔ one failure does not strand the rest, and is carried back with its error (0.5174ms)
✔ Stop finishes the one in hand and starts no more (0.3807ms)
✔ Stop before the first one starts nothing (0.2597ms)
✔ an empty list is a run that did nothing, not an error (0.2378ms)
✔ onStart names who is being worked on, before the work (0.2582ms)
✔ a person with no name still reads as a person (0.1303ms)
✔ the summary of a clean run is just the count (0.2394ms)
✔ the summary names failures rather than counting them (0.5774ms)
✔ a stopped run says how many were never started (0.5872ms)
✔ a long list of failures counts the tail instead of running off the line (0.848ms)
✔ the total defaults to everything the run knows about (0.4475ms)
(node:404) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ jobs file under their client and the month they were raised (6.6935ms)
✔ the month comes from the local clock, and falls back sanely (1.1304ms)
✔ a second file of the same name in one folder is numbered (0.728ms)
✔ csv cells are quoted and never formulas (0.717ms)
✔ the zip is named for what it holds (0.515ms)
✔ an archived ticket keeps the rate it was billed at, and the summary agrees with the invoice (69.4555ms)
✔ a ticket filed before the snapshot existed still reads the client's rate (0.5815ms)
✔ the job text file carries the record, the money and the crew (15.8576ms)
✔ the downloaded zip checks out when it is the one that was built (4.6272ms)
✔ a byte changed inside a file is caught (4.7272ms)
✔ a zip past what its trailer can count is refused, never written short (1469.3092ms)
✔ the drift check sees a swap that leaves every count the same (0.6819ms)
✔ a file left out of the download is caught, and so is one that isn't from this build (1.4494ms)
✔ a complete build says so and holds every job's paperwork (5.5416ms)
✔ a read the network could not answer is a gap in the archive, not an empty job (62.6506ms)
✔ anything served from this device's memory during a build is flagged too (2.7191ms)
✔ a ticket read that fails is a gap, not the end of the build (3.0142ms)
✔ an invoice that would not render is a named gap, and the ticket is still archived (2.5715ms)
✔ a report PDF that would not download is a named gap too (2.698ms)
✔ the build records what each job held, for the clear to check against (2.0636ms)
✔ a job that has gained work since the build stops the clear (0.4164ms)
✔ a minted duplicate name never collides with a file really called that (0.4429ms)
✔ mapLimit runs a few at a time and answers in order (56.7823ms)
✔ something that isn't a zip is said to be so (0.6427ms)
(node:30036) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askDrafts.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ pickTemplate reads the kind of work out of the words (3.696ms)
✔ a job draft needs the project and the LSD, and says which is missing (1.2415ms)
✔ a job draft is the dialog's seed and one sentence (1.8419ms)
✔ a ticket draft cleans its lines and date (0.9507ms)
✔ a JHA draft keeps only real hazards and string site fields (0.8528ms)
✔ csv: every cell quoted, formulas made text, a BOM in front, columns first (3.4919ms)
✔ html: scripts, handlers and javascript: urls go; the page stays (1.5213ms)
✔ sizes read as bytes, KB or MB (0.2755ms)
✔ a workbook is one worksheet per sheet with the columns as the first row (1.8456ms)
✔ a pdf writes the title, the sections and their tables down the page and over page breaks (1.483ms)
(node:26628) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askFiles.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the name keeps the person's words, drops what a filesystem refuses, and takes the kind's extension (4.375ms)
✔ html and css are text, bounded (1.7325ms)
✔ csv is one table, every row as wide as the columns, cells kept as strings or numbers (4.7066ms)
✔ xlsx is one to ten sheets, names made safe and unique, rows counted across sheets (3.0992ms)
✔ pdf is a titled document of sections, each with something in it (1.2165ms)
✔ the words name the file and what is in it, and the size is a rough count (1.3811ms)
(node:27032) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askKnowledge.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Ask knows every screen in TABS by its key and label, and no other (2.8745ms)
✔ the knowledge block names every screen and stays a page, not a manual (3.0657ms)
✔ the context is checked and cut to size, never trusted (1.0663ms)
✔ the where line names the screen, the job and the ticket, and wraps the help as data (0.9111ms)
(node:484) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askLearn.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the extractor is told to keep how the app works and nothing about records or people (3.8107ms)
✔ the answer is read strictly: JSON or nothing, bounded, deduplicated, replaces only notes that exist (3.6549ms)
✔ the cap holds: room for new notes is what is left under MAX_LEARNED (0.4598ms)
✔ the notes enter the prompt graded by the speaker's role now, wrapped as data; none means nothing (0.8464ms)
✔ forgetting is worded from the note, shortened when long (0.6807ms)
(node:11356) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askLoop.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ windowTurns keeps the last 24, clips long turns and ends on the question (19.9401ms)
✔ a plain answer comes straight back, with the key in the header and no tools sent when none are offered (110.1087ms)
✔ a tool call is run, its answer sent back as records, and the trace says so (3.5048ms)
✔ a read that fails is handed back as an error result and the loop goes on (3.0401ms)
✔ past the call limit the model is asked to answer with no tool allowed (9.202ms)
✔ past the time budget the next request allows no tool either (1.7068ms)
✔ the API's refusals become plain words and never carry the key (2.5285ms)
✔ an answer with no words still says something (0.9559ms)
✔ the system prompt names the person, the day in Grande Prairie and the rules (95.6948ms)
✔ wrapRecords says what the records are and that they are data (1.6019ms)
(node:25768) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askSends.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ a name resolves to the one contact on file, exact first, then by containment (4.6002ms)
✔ unknown, ambiguous and no-email names refuse, naming the person (1.5587ms)
✔ a bare address passes only when the person typed it, case-insensitively (1.6738ms)
✔ addresses are deduped and capped at the transport's limit (2.9062ms)
✔ the JHA gate is send-jha's: a PDF, and the signer or a sending role (1.2642ms)
✔ the ticket gate is send-ticket-approval's: unsigned, something on it, own or the office (5.9063ms)
✔ a ticket approval goes to the ticket's contact, else the job's rep, else refuses (1.6223ms)
✔ the words name the file, the job and every address, and say again when it is (2.3099ms)
✔ an answer keeps what was learned, and the × drops one note from the turn alone (7.0724ms)
✔ a proposal the card confirms in place is told from a draft by its kind, and the button says what it does (0.6165ms)
✔ an action rides the answer turn for the card, never the send, and Not now drops it (0.7056ms)
✔ foldTranscripts takes segments in order and cumulative repeats once (0.5935ms)
✔ dictation rebuilds the box from what was typed plus what was said (0.6191ms)
✔ a thread is turns in order, trace kept beside the answer and not sent (0.5179ms)
✔ only the last ASK_KEEP turns are kept (0.5172ms)
✔ jobLinks marks real job numbers by membership, never by pattern (0.8537ms)
(node:27408) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askTools.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ every tool sits behind a tab the app has (2.8131ms)
✔ toolsFor offers exactly the tools behind the tabs held, and the price roles for a ticket (11.5622ms)
✔ the lists and the JHA send sit behind job; the ticket send behind ticket and a price role (1.6352ms)
✔ the timer tools sit behind job, and the kinds are scheduledSends.ts's (1.7737ms)
✔ the definitions carry only what the API takes (2.0812ms)
✔ the templates and hazard names are data.js's, word for word (0.4691ms)
✔ searchArgs cleans what the model sends (0.8959ms)
✔ a trace line says what was read or drafted, in words (1.4825ms)
✔ make_file is for anyone holding a tab, never an account with none, and its kinds are askFiles.ts's (37.1058ms)
✔ the six helpers sit behind their screens, and the equipment filters are the screen's own (3.5703ms)
✔ the five more sit behind their screens and roles (1.5683ms)
(node:16824) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/emailIn.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
(node:16824) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
✔ the address rule is the same code on the screens and in the function (5.8422ms)
✔ the chase plan is the same code on the tracker and in the function (39.9668ms)
✔ the card's words name the due tickets and who is left alone and why; nothing due is a refusal (3.1138ms)
✔ Home's attention questions are the same code on the board and in the function (7.312ms)
✔ an ordinary morning says nothing (9.1481ms)
✔ nothing read at all is nothing to say, not a crash (0.5104ms)
✔ a failed backup names the failure but keeps the raw error off the board (2.2139ms)
✔ a failed restore is not called a backup (0.5814ms)
✔ a failed file check is not called a backup either (0.5907ms)
✔ a run that finished is not news (0.66ms)
✔ a lapsed drive connection is the first thing said (0.6194ms)
✔ a due date well in the past means nothing is picking the schedule up (0.583ms)
✔ a backup a little late is not late enough to say (0.5252ms)
✔ a drive that was never connected has no schedule to be late for (0.798ms)
✔ background errors inside the day are counted and grouped by function (1.1738ms)
✔ errors older than the day are left out, and one error is singular (0.5054ms)
✔ a row stamped a minute ahead of this device's clock still counts (0.4003ms)
✔ agoPhrase reads like a person saying it (0.7114ms)
✔ the signature is steady for one state and empty when there is nothing to say (0.7962ms)
✔ a new error, or one more of them, moves the signature (0.7415ms)
✔ a dismissed strip stays down until its signature changes (0.5609ms)
✔ nothing to say is never suppressed, and nothing is written for a non-signature (0.45ms)
✔ a failed file check does not send the office to a button that is not there (0.4583ms)
✔ clearing a dismissal forgets the signature, so the same trouble returning is news again (0.3712ms)
✔ the digest's kind words are the strip's, read back from the function (1.8761ms)
(node:32520) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/backupRun.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ only buckets whose keys are never reused are carried over (4.0995ms)
✔ an object is carried over when the base holds its name at the same size (0.8062ms)
✔ a rewritable bucket is never carried over, even on a perfect match (0.5017ms)
✔ the base is the newest stamped folder that is not this run's own (0.7321ms)
✔ the cursor remembers the base it chose, and that it looked (1.0167ms)
✔ a paused page and a finished page both carry the reused count (0.7694ms)
✔ the panel says how many were carried over, and nothing when none were (0.4261ms)
✔ a copy with no recorded hash is not carried over — it is read through and hashed (0.3848ms)
✔ the redirect URI is the stored app address plus the provider (5.2795ms)
✔ only the origin of the stored address counts — a path or a trailing slash is dropped (0.6191ms)
✔ with no address stored, this window's origin is the honest guess (0.459ms)
✔ a stored address that isn't a URL falls back rather than throwing (0.6028ms)
✔ the three providers, and each with a name a person would recognise (2.5587ms)
✔ a blank secret box leaves the stored secret alone — the column is not in the patch at all (1.6825ms)
✔ a typed secret is written, trimmed (0.6136ms)
✔ whitespace alone is still blank — it does not erase a stored secret (0.4646ms)
✔ client IDs are trimmed, and an emptied box does clear the column (1.1792ms)
✔ the schedule is clamped to what the database's own checks allow (0.7764ms)
✔ nonsense in the number boxes lands on the defaults rather than on NaN (0.5416ms)
✔ the sentence under the keep box says the number the save would write (0.4926ms)
✔ one kept backup is “the most recent one”, not “the 1 most recents” (0.5112ms)
✔ the four frequencies the schedule knows all survive (0.4176ms)
✔ the next run is only worked out once there is a drive to run to (1.7379ms)
✔ the patch names the one row and stamps it (0.3494ms)
✔ the patch never carries a refresh token, an account or a provider — those are the callback's (0.3494ms)
✔ a connected callback is read, and the query it came home with is taken off (0.4688ms)
✔ a refusal carries the function's own words (0.3016ms)
✔ a cancelled consent screen is not an error (0.1924ms)
✔ anything else on the address bar is left where it was (0.2695ms)
✔ no backup query at all means there is nothing to say (0.3098ms)
✔ an outcome word we don't know is treated as a failure, not as success (0.2444ms)
✔ the reason a connection failed survives the reload that follows it (1.7609ms)
✔ a refresh of the backup state does not rewrite the schedule boxes (1.2552ms)
✔ a before-restore copy is recognised by the same prefix the server writes (0.9345ms)
✔ the restore is confirmed by the backup's own name, character for character (0.3661ms)
✔ a failed backup says the schedule carries it; a failed restore says where the app is (0.5671ms)
✔ a restore-all that failed after the wipe names both ways out (0.3621ms)
✔ a restore-all that failed before the wipe says nothing has been changed (0.363ms)
✔ a per-job restore that failed touched nothing else (0.2668ms)
✔ a Google client id pasted with the console's helper text is reduced to the id (0.5307ms)
✔ a run's figures come out of counts, and a run with none reads as zero (0.5741ms)
✔ one run is not a trend (0.7862ms)
✔ the line runs oldest to newest and is scaled from zero, so half is half (0.5915ms)
✔ a backup that halved says so; one that held steady does not (0.5084ms)
✔ only runs that wrote a copy are plotted (0.4518ms)
✔ a file check reads as one sentence, and says when there was nothing to repair (0.8263ms)
✔ the panel lists only the notes the file check's sentence has not already said (15.0803ms)
(node:5700) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/backupRestore.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the phases run safety, wipe, accounts, tables, files, activity (7.8486ms)
✔ a fresh cursor starts at safety and remembers who is driving (0.7698ms)
✔ a cursor read back out of jsonb is filled in rather than trusted (1.2377ms)
✔ the counts always carry skipped and collisions, at zero if nothing else (0.8965ms)
✔ the counts carry the safety copy's name, because a failed restore is read from them (2.736ms)
✔ a retry reuses the last attempt's safety copy rather than copying the damage (4.2256ms)
✔ the reused copy is named on the run, and the panel reads that list (2.4354ms)
✔ the wipe deletes in batches, and remembers the size and what it took (0.8173ms)
✔ a batch the cap cancels is halved, and only the floor is a failure (0.7249ms)
✔ only a statement timeout is answered by trying again with less (1.1399ms)
✔ the wipe's delete is bounded, and goes through the definer RPC (7.5546ms)
✔ the wipe walks its list once and then hands over to accounts (0.7257ms)
✔ only profiles keeps a row back, and it is the caller's (0.48ms)
✔ rate_lines is emptied before its history, and the restore says why (1.4459ms)
✔ a part loaded adds to the count; the last one moves to the next table (0.67ms)
✔ the last table hands over to the files (0.3434ms)
✔ chat history rewinds for its second pass and only then moves on (0.2632ms)
✔ a table's parts are its own, and rate_lines never takes the history's (37.2186ms)
✔ auth_email comes off before a profile row is written (0.522ms)
✔ a profile row whose account could not be made is left out of the load (0.7137ms)
✔ a row that cannot stand without that person goes; a row that can is blanked (1.3856ms)
✔ a table that never names a profile is not filtered at all (0.368ms)
✔ a reaction to a message that was left out is left out with it (0.5172ms)
✔ every NOT NULL key into a table the restore can thin is named (0.3608ms)
✔ a part's skipped rows are counted once, however often a slice resumes (0.3396ms)
✔ a deactivated account is re-created but is not invited back in (0.2614ms)
✔ the people left out are named on the run itself (8.3354ms)
✔ an account that only missed its email is not written down as an account that was lost (0.7623ms)
✔ the mail failures are marked as they are pushed, not guessed at afterwards (2.2735ms)
✔ a restore that raised its safety backup starts it rather than waiting for the cron (1.7092ms)
✔ pass one empties every quote and drops the ids already on the table (0.9258ms)
✔ pass two writes only the quotes, and only where there is one (0.5563ms)
✔ a reply whose quoted message was left out keeps its own words (0.4825ms)
✔ the live Resend and KLIPY keys survive a restore (0.5423ms)
✔ a backup taken before the keys were stripped restores them like any column (2.4819ms)
✔ every column the backup blanks is one the restore skips or never writes (0.4854ms)
✔ the settings row a fresh project has never had is created, not silently skipped (1.4292ms)
✔ a ticket goes back in at zero, because its lines are not there yet (0.5621ms)
✔ only a signed or invoiced ticket gets its own total written back (0.7669ms)
✔ the restore remembers whether it has done the totals (0.7714ms)
✔ only the jobs that had an activity time get one back (0.5763ms)
✔ a report put back is still a PDF (0.473ms)
✔ the typed name is the backup's own, character for character (0.3519ms)
✔ the refusals say what to do about them (0.401ms)
✔ rows go back in batches small enough for PostgREST to take (0.3351ms)
✔ the restore keeps the gates it is supposed to keep (2.1921ms)
✔ the three column patches go through the RPC, never an upsert (3.4519ms)
✔ a restore waiting on its safety backup still says it is alive (1.8318ms)
✔ an orphaned child is filtered against the rows that actually landed (1.4483ms)
✔ a per-job restore has no safety phase and no wipe (0.2897ms)
✔ the two cursors are told apart by the kind written on them (1.0691ms)
✔ this kind's counts carry the notes themselves, not a tally (0.9293ms)
✔ the notes stop before the cursor stops fitting, and say so (0.4236ms)
✔ a part is filtered to the chosen jobs, and children to what landed (0.8949ms)
✔ every table a job's records live in is one this filter has an answer for (0.4146ms)
✔ a job already here is left alone, and a number in use is a collision (0.9078ms)
✔ a job that is already here is still a job its missing records go under (0.4705ms)
✔ a run whose chosen jobs are none of them here stops after the jobs table (0.3968ms)
✔ the per-job cursor carries the jobs it found already here (0.5432ms)
✔ a ticket number already in use, or retired, is reported and skipped (0.7382ms)
✔ the same ticket back on the same job is left alone, not called a collision (0.7722ms)
✔ a save key already in use is named, not left to a raw constraint (1.3836ms)
✔ a child row already here is left alone, and said once for the table (1.3464ms)
✔ one of something reads as one of something, in the office's own words (0.7349ms)
✔ a crew row whose person has gone is skipped and counted out loud (0.7576ms)
✔ a name on a row that stands without it is blanked, not dropped (0.4064ms)
✔ a client is kept by id, matched by name, or reported lost (0.6378ms)
✔ a contact is matched inside the organisation the job ended up with (0.6716ms)
✔ only the PDFs the restored rows actually point at are fetched (0.4427ms)
✔ the totals and dates are put back only on the rows this run wrote (1.2119ms)
✔ a per-job restore walks part by part and table by table (0.6037ms)
✔ restoring a few jobs deletes nothing and overwrites nothing (2.3479ms)
✔ a restored ticket goes in at zero and is re-priced from its lines (4.6348ms)
✔ a job already in the app is a parent the children still follow (1.9046ms)
✔ a save key already in use is checked for before the batch, not after (1.8342ms)
✔ a damaged file is counted on both cursors and reaches the panel's counts (0.63ms)
✔ a damaged file is left out rather than written over a good one (2.3918ms)
(node:8396) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the zone is the crew's own (3.1389ms)
✔ zonedFields reads Grande Prairie's wall clock, not UTC's (3.3416ms)
✔ zonedFields calls midnight hour 0, never 24 (0.513ms)
✔ instantAt lands on the wall clock in winter and in summer (0.7532ms)
✔ instantAt on the spring-forward morning gives the first real moment (1.138ms)
✔ instantAt on the fall-back morning takes the first of the two 01:00s (0.5036ms)
✔ matchesDay knows each frequency (0.7042ms)
✔ daily rolls to tomorrow once today's hour has gone (1.1464ms)
✔ daily never returns the instant it was asked at (0.6932ms)
✔ weekdays skips Saturday and Sunday (1.0804ms)
✔ weekly waits for its own day (3.3031ms)
✔ weekly asked on its own day before the hour keeps today (0.6894ms)
✔ monthly means the 1st, across a month end and a year end (1.0281ms)
✔ a daily 02:00 still fires on the morning 02:00 does not exist (0.6195ms)
✔ a daily 01:00 fires once on the morning 01:00 happens twice (0.4702ms)
✔ rubbish settings fall back to a daily midnight rather than throwing (0.8413ms)
✔ describeSchedule says it in words a person reads (0.4631ms)
✔ the panel's schedule and the function's are the same code (141.8927ms)
(node:4284) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/backupTables.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ every backed-up table is also a loaded table, and the other way round (7.7901ms)
✔ the spec's table list is what is actually backed up (2.254ms)
✔ parents come before their children in the load order (0.9927ms)
✔ the wipe order is the handover script's own order (9.4776ms)
✔ rate_lines is emptied before its history, because deleting one writes the other (5.6815ms)
✔ everything loaded is wiped first, except the settings row (0.6323ms)
✔ profiles is wiped last, because everything else names it (0.6304ms)
✔ the wipe clears the two log tables the backup does not carry (0.6885ms)
✔ every table has a primary key and a paging answer (6.7476ms)
✔ only the composite-key tables page by offset (0.7496ms)
✔ the buckets are the five the app actually stores in (10.6122ms)
✔ the app_settings column scan finds the columns the migrations added (314.8095ms)
✔ every credential column of app_settings is stripped from a backup (345.1719ms)
✔ stripSecrets empties the settings row's credentials and leaves the rest (0.8376ms)
✔ stripSecrets leaves every other table exactly as it found it (0.6195ms)
✔ a restore never writes back the drive connection it is running through (148.4353ms)
✔ the page size is PostgREST's own silent cap (0.208ms)
✔ chunkRows splits at the cap and never drops or duplicates a row (1.5352ms)
✔ part files are flat names, numbered from one, that sort in order (0.5222ms)
✔ a stored object's name survives the round trip through the drive (0.5397ms)
✔ restoring chosen jobs reaches for exactly the tables a job owns (0.1736ms)
✔ a folder is stamped on Grande Prairie's clock (0.559ms)
✔ a manifest records what went in and says what it holds (0.899ms)
✔ recordFiles adds up across the slices a run is made of (0.3142ms)
✔ the jobs index is what the per-job restore picks from (1.0452ms)
✔ a before-restore copy stops at the manifest and never prunes the drive (0.3573ms)
✔ retention spares the folder a restore is reading from, however old (0.7488ms)
✔ retention keeps the newest N and throws the rest away (0.2987ms)
✔ retention reads the folders in date order however they arrive (0.1398ms)
✔ retention never touches a before-restore folder (0.1896ms)
✔ a backup from a newer schema than the live one is refused (0.143ms)
✔ the fake drive answers the whole interface (1.2245ms)
✔ the fake drive overwrites a name rather than doubling it, as the real three do (0.4607ms)
✔ deleting a folder takes what is inside it (1.201ms)
✔ the fake can be told to fail, so retries can be tested (0.7585ms)
✔ Google resumes where the 308 says it got to, not where the sender hoped (74.5949ms)
✔ a 308 with no Range at all is Google saying it took the whole chunk (7.7024ms)
✔ Google asks about the one name it is about to write, not the whole folder (6.5394ms)
✔ an apostrophe in a name does not become a Drive query syntax error (3.1251ms)
✔ Google looks for the folder rather than making a second one of the same name (1.4752ms)
✔ Google creates the folder when the lookup finds none (1.2743ms)
✔ OneDrive resumes where nextExpectedRanges says it got to, not where the sender hoped (2.0024ms)
✔ a 202 with no ranges on it is OneDrive saying it took the whole chunk (1.3539ms)
✔ OneDrive gives up on a session that keeps none of two identical chunks (1.4289ms)
✔ OneDrive creates a folder fail-on-conflict, and looks it up rather than replacing it (1.6202ms)
✔ Dropbox returns the folder it finds rather than asking to create it (0.8737ms)
✔ Dropbox creates the folder when the path is free (1.0599ms)
✔ the three providers are asked for exactly the scopes the spec names (0.2847ms)
✔ each authorize URL carries the state, the redirect and offline access (0.7773ms)
✔ an unknown provider is refused rather than guessed at (0.4338ms)
✔ the provider is the last segment of the callback's path, and only if we know it (0.2296ms)
✔ the callback URI is built from the stored app address, origin only (0.3532ms)
✔ the panel and the function build the same string from the same stored address (0.3195ms)
✔ with no app address stored the server refuses rather than guessing (0.6516ms)
✔ credentials come out of the row by provider, and an incomplete pair is refused (0.7872ms)
✔ the three provider lists are one list written three times (0.3093ms)
✔ the callback spends the nonce it was handed and no other (1.3279ms)
✔ a drive's own refusal is retold rather than repeated into the address bar (1.4509ms)
✔ the nonce has to be the one we minted (0.4548ms)
✔ the nonce goes stale at ten minutes (0.2273ms)
✔ the shared modules read nothing from the world around them (8.8747ms)
✔ a table part survives being gzipped and read back (53.4023ms)
✔ an empty table still round-trips (3.6828ms)
✔ a slice's budget is spent against its own deadline (0.4689ms)
✔ a heartbeat older than a slice can live is a run to reclaim (0.6442ms)
✔ the wipe empties tickets before the list their numbers are burned into (0.8249ms)
✔ the walk of the account list stops on an empty page, not a short one (1.8948ms)
✔ the chain that drives a backup asks for the run it just moved (1.3838ms)
✔ a restore waiting on its safety backup is tended by whichever slice moved the copy (1.2473ms)
✔ a slice that matched no row has lost the run and must stop writing (0.2631ms)
✔ a gateway page is named plainly, and anything else keeps its own words (0.7537ms)
✔ every write a slice makes to its own run is conditional on still holding it (1.8159ms)
✔ the kick is held open by the runtime rather than left to be reaped (0.7467ms)
✔ only the flag on a drive's refusal earns a retry (0.6706ms)
✔ the token endpoint gets one more kind of second chance than a drive does (0.3862ms)
✔ a passing edge error is transient; a real refusal is not (0.5608ms)
✔ a run is left for reclaim only while it is young enough to still finish (0.2164ms)
✔ a transient edge blip mid-slice leaves the run for the next tick, not failed (0.9696ms)
✔ connectDrive's refresh is under the same three goes as everything else (0.6798ms)
✔ a table that is not finished continues from the key the walk reached (0.6651ms)
✔ the last table hands the run to the files phase (0.1833ms)
✔ an empty table is still a part, so the manifest can say zero (0.1552ms)
✔ the jobs index is folded out of the rows the tables phase reads (0.6536ms)
✔ a bucket is walked depth first and the stack says where it got to (0.5006ms)
✔ a page cut short by the budget resumes where it stopped (0.2292ms)
✔ a cursor read back out of jsonb is filled in rather than trusted (0.7296ms)
✔ the counts the panel shows are the cursor's own (0.4915ms)
✔ a file is hashed the way the index and a restore will compare it (13.29ms)
✔ the file index reads back only records that carry a hash (1.1151ms)
✔ the manifest records how many files are hashed, where, and the spot check (0.3799ms)
✔ a file check's cursor starts empty, revives from jsonb, and its counts read as the panel needs (0.5944ms)
✔ a file check's notes are capped, and the cap says so once (0.326ms)
✔ the next file check is a whole number of days on, fourteen when the setting is nonsense (0.2193ms)
✔ a file the drive would not hand over is left alone by the check, not re-stored over (1.0009ms)
✔ a run row that could not be made puts the clock back, for both clocks (1.1238ms)
✔ a due time that already has its run is not queued a second one, for both clocks (1.3937ms)
✔ the file rows are reconciled with the folder before the index is written from them (1.6196ms)
✔ crew hours and dose are stored at the precision their columns hold (4.4947ms)
✔ the crew write names the precision of every column it fills (2.1237ms)
✔ the crew boxes and the billing boxes ask for different precision (0.9516ms)
✔ ticket writes preserve legacy quantity/rate precision and price the stored values (4.0735ms)
(node:31572) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the app's line arithmetic and the invoice's are the same code (7.0003ms)
✔ a line's charge is what the database would compute, at any scale (1.9837ms)
✔ a rate the rate card no longer offers is still billed at what it was filed at (0.4707ms)
✔ the invoice's subtotal is the sum of its own printed lines (0.9923ms)
✔ GST is a percentage of whole cents, rounded half away from zero (0.6285ms)
✔ all three GST call sites answer the same, to the cent (12.1127ms)
✔ a missing GST rate is five percent and never an exemption (0.4976ms)
✔ storedNumber rounds the way the column rounds, not the way toFixed does (1.353ms)
✔ exactRound is half away from zero, and answers zero for what is not a number (0.6371ms)
✔ saving a ticket preserves a line's precision rather than refusing it (4.0226ms)
✔ a ticket with a rep and no history is due, with the address its link goes to (17.8646ms)
✔ a rep with a question open is left alone, not chased (3.5415ms)
✔ chased inside the window is skipped; chased outside it is due again (0.9718ms)
✔ a label with no address in it cannot be chased and is counted separately (0.8899ms)
✔ a ticket with no contact at all is a no-email skip, not a crash (0.7358ms)
✔ the reasons are exclusive and tested in order: queried wins over recent and over no email (0.6515ms)
✔ recent wins over no email — the ticket is not due either way (0.6636ms)
✔ the due list keeps the order it was read in, because the dialog lists it (0.739ms)
✔ nothing unsigned means four empty buckets, not a thrown dialog (0.8904ms)
✔ the composer is held whole, per account, and emptied piece by piece (3.0795ms)
✔ a new message is added in order (5.1024ms)
✔ an unchanged refresh returns the same array identity (0.5676ms)
✔ a realtime copy without joins keeps the name it cannot carry (0.3516ms)
✔ the Someone bug: a corrected quote is allowed to land (0.5513ms)
✔ a nameless provisional cannot overwrite a named quote (1.0653ms)
✔ an authoritative null quote clears a deleted parent's text (0.6449ms)
✔ a realtime null quote (no join) keeps the resolved quote (0.7333ms)
✔ null reactions mean unknown; an array is authoritative (0.675ms)
✔ a pin change alone is a change (0.9044ms)
✔ ordering is stable on identical timestamps (0.9403ms)
✔ the keys tell apart what matters and ignore order (0.5647ms)
✔ a message deleted inside the page's window leaves the room (1.0082ms)
✔ history older than the page is not the page's to judge (0.5048ms)
✔ a send that landed after the fetch was asked for is kept (0.6775ms)
✔ a stale cached page cannot delete what arrived after it (0.5173ms)
✔ an empty page removes nothing (0.5127ms)
(node:17964) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/constantTime.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ secretsMatch answers equality, and an unminted secret matches nothing (3.7753ms)
✔ secretsMatch walks every presented byte and never returns from inside the walk (3.5335ms)
✔ every door compares its secret through secretsMatch, never with an operator (29.9497ms)
✔ money always shows two decimals and groups thousands (73.3936ms)
✔ money treats nonsense as zero rather than printing NaN at a client (1.6064ms)
✔ todayLocal is the local day, morning and evening alike (3.4228ms)
✔ todayLocal does not follow UTC over the day boundary (1.2034ms)
✔ todayLocal pads a single-digit month and day (0.6479ms)
✔ contacts is added to any account that has access at all (2.519ms)
✔ an account already holding contacts does not get it twice (0.4876ms)
✔ no tabs stays no tabs — the universal one never unlocks an empty account (0.4894ms)
✔ tabList hands back a new list rather than editing the profile's (0.5616ms)
✔ the primary is the one that comes back (0.9309ms)
✔ an org id is not enough — the type has to match too (1.4625ms)
✔ with nobody promoted, the first on file stands in (0.599ms)
✔ nothing to answer with is null, never a stranger (0.2585ms)
✔ a helper is a Helper and everyone else is a Technician (0.2366ms)
✔ an unknown or missing rank falls to Technician, not to nothing (0.2352ms)
✔ prices are an Admin's and a Technician's (0.1873ms)
✔ nobody else sees a price, including nobody at all (0.157ms)
✔ an approved or invoiced ticket refuses a save outright (0.6545ms)
✔ a Draft save over a ticket sent for signature is refused (0.5605ms)
✔ an ordinary draft save is not refused (0.396ms)
✔ fileSize names the unit the file is actually in (0.4215ms)
✔ a non-PDF is refused by name, and says what to do (0.5372ms)
✔ a PDF the browser gave no type for is still a PDF (0.2666ms)
✔ an oversized PDF is refused with its own size and the limit (0.1953ms)
✔ no file is not a refusal (0.124ms)
✔ the sanity ceiling is per unit, with a default for anything new (0.3085ms)
✔ a client with no rate on file is billed the ordinary 5% (0.5515ms)
✔ gstOn with no rate given still charges 5% (1.3659ms)
✔ an exempt client is charged nothing, not a rounding of nothing (0.4494ms)
✔ the half-cent rounds up at every rate, so the company is not short (0.4657ms)
✔ a missing rate is charged, never quietly exempted (0.6428ms)
✔ the rate is written so a technician can tell exempt from broken (0.4196ms)
✔ the JHA's standing hazards open unticked (0.3834ms)
✔ ROLE_PRESETS matches tabs_for_role() in the migrations (530.1903ms)
✔ no unapplied handover SQL quietly redefines tabs_for_role (170.3569ms)
✔ a line total rounds the way tickets.total does (0.6882ms)
✔ localDate reads a plain date as local, not UTC (8.8027ms)
✔ localDate sits at midday so a DST shift cannot move the day (0.8795ms)
✔ localDate on rubbish gives an invalid date rather than a wrong one (1.1948ms)
✔ ticketDateStamp is MMDD-YY and pads (0.5544ms)
✔ dayMonth is a padded day and a short month, no full stop (59.2415ms)
✔ initialsOf gives letters only, capped at three (0.9061ms)
✔ initialsOf survives names the ticket number would otherwise choke on (5.1694ms)
✔ the 15th is the last day of the first half (2.8818ms)
✔ the 16th starts the second half (0.5716ms)
✔ the second half ends on the real last day of the month (0.6781ms)
✔ periods walk backwards without skipping or repeating (0.6039ms)
✔ every period is contiguous with the one before it (0.6701ms)
✔ no period is ever empty or inverted (0.5395ms)
✔ payPeriodLabel reads as a date range with the year once (2.1368ms)
✔ hours always shows two decimals (0.5881ms)
✔ hours treats nonsense as zero rather than NaN on a timesheet (0.4038ms)
✔ ageInDays counts from local midnight, not elapsed hours (0.9ms)
✔ ageInDays is zero for nothing rather than NaN (0.2489ms)
✔ GST is five percent (0.1549ms)
✔ GST rounds a half-cent up, not down (1.0356ms)
✔ GST on ordinary amounts is exact (0.3562ms)
✔ no whole-cent subtotal is ever mis-rounded (411.8887ms)
✔ a sub-cent product rounds to the cent (0.4956ms)
✔ exact products pass through untouched (0.3325ms)
✔ float dust cannot reach a bill (0.2223ms)
✔ nothing times anything is nothing (0.2652ms)
✔ GST on a rounded-line subtotal lands on the cent (0.244ms)
✔ comma decimals are decimals (0.5095ms)
✔ negatives floor to zero (0.2445ms)
✔ garbage floors to zero (0.2003ms)
(node:30360) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/dayCheck.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ a day with everything filed and sent is done, with nothing missing (7.1492ms)
✔ each gap is its own phrase, filed-but-not-sent apart from not filed (1.2315ms)
✔ no helper on the ticket is a note, not a gap — working alone is a real day (0.7025ms)
✔ the day's furthest-along ticket is the one judged; a sent stamp on a draft counts as sent (1.1496ms)
✔ a kit with nothing in it is the one worth asking about (2.5012ms)
✔ spaces are not a serial (0.4115ms)
✔ one serial is enough to leave the worker alone (0.5078ms)
✔ all three go to the profile, trimmed, blanks included (2.3956ms)
✔ a missing function is recognised by code and by name (0.7622ms)
✔ a refusal, a timeout and a silence are not a missing function (5.6028ms)
✔ a typed serial is news only when the profile does not hold it (1.1569ms)
✔ every screen in TABS has a help entry (4.6644ms)
✔ no help entry names a screen that no longer exists (3.0867ms)
✔ every entry carries a heading and at least one paragraph (0.979ms)
✔ no entry runs past six paragraphs or two hundred words (2.0065ms)
✔ helpFor answers null for a screen with no entry, so a screen can open with no tip (0.4716ms)
✔ a screen speaks once a run, and the other screens still speak (3.1522ms)
✔ the next run of the app starts the tips over (1.8934ms)
✔ no more tips is the kill switch, this account alone (2.5107ms)
✔ a record that is not the word yes leaves the help where it is (0.5075ms)
✔ no account and no screen mean nothing is owed; a missing run does not (0.4822ms)
(node:32880) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/hoursDose.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ periods refuse nonexistent dates before a database read (7.9854ms)
✔ today is Grande Prairie's date, not UTC's (57.7997ms)
✔ a pay period is the 1st to the 15th or the 16th to the month's end, February included (3.3651ms)
✔ a quarter is the calendar quarter (0.8805ms)
✔ the range is both ends or neither; half a range, a backwards one or more than a year is refused (1.1038ms)
✔ hours sum per job and in total in whole hundredths, days as distinct work dates (1.7125ms)
(node:32908) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ invoice and approval totals retain the stamped rate when the client's rate changes (6.7938ms)
✔ legacy invoices without a snapshot keep their existing fallback behavior (0.8114ms)
✔ the real invoice loader fetches the snapshot before rendering the approved copy (8.652ms)
✔ approval freezes the rate before sending so the subsequent page cannot change its total (83.4129ms)
✔ a snapshot failure stops the email and token write (1.6362ms)
✔ resending retains an existing exempt rate (1.8452ms)
✔ mail failure does not mark approval sent, but retains the reserved rate for retry (1.627ms)
✔ an unbroken run of film numbers becomes a range (13.4142ms)
✔ a gap splits the runs instead of being papered over (0.9236ms)
✔ several gaps, several runs (0.5226ms)
✔ a single number stands alone rather than as a range to itself (0.4778ms)
✔ both prefixes, XF first regardless of document order (0.4739ms)
✔ the unhyphenated procedure designation does not count (0.3687ms)
✔ the hyphenated, zero-padded procedure does not count either (0.6288ms)
✔ a number followed by REV is paperwork whatever its padding (0.7964ms)
✔ zero-padded numbers are dropped even without REV after them (0.5698ms)
✔ duplicates collapse and order does not matter (0.8748ms)
✔ case survives a sloppy report (0.5069ms)
✔ ultrasonic and the radiographic variants count too (3.1238ms)
✔ the UT procedure pulls the same trick and meets the same guards (0.3589ms)
✔ every prefix reports in paperwork order regardless of page order (0.2882ms)
✔ film numbers in the hundreds, straight off a real report (0.5431ms)
✔ no numbers means an empty answer, not a broken one (0.299ms)
✔ lookalikes without the word boundary stay out (0.9809ms)
✔ fractional quantities stop at thousandths without treating step as an increment (3.935ms)
✔ money has an explicit two-place limit, including decimal commas (0.8762ms)
✔ an exponent is refused, not swallowed (0.4909ms)
✔ a second decimal point is refused rather than shown (0.4598ms)
✔ a minus sign is refused and never becomes a positive (0.5186ms)
✔ a comma decimal is a decimal (0.9009ms)
✔ a grouping comma survives a whole-unit step (0.8776ms)
✔ step decides whether a decimal point is a key at all (0.5136ms)
✔ an emptied box stays empty (0.6054ms)
✔ letters and emoji are refused whole (1.1888ms)
✔ isWholeStep reads the props the callers actually pass (0.5559ms)
✔ a decimal comma is a decimal point (3.5876ms)
✔ a comma before three trailing digits is a thousands separator (0.6547ms)
✔ …unless nothing that could be thousands precedes it (0.5078ms)
✔ with both marks present the last one is the decimal point (0.43ms)
✔ plain numbers pass through untouched (0.418ms)
✔ nothing, rubbish and negatives floor to zero (0.3125ms)
✔ a read that answers is the answer, and it is remembered (39.3786ms)
✔ with the signal gone, the remembered copy is served — and says so (17.1109ms)
✔ nothing remembered means the failure surfaces (4.4305ms)
✔ a real answer from the server is never replaced by a remembered one (2.8509ms)
✔ a plain failure while the browser knows it is offline still serves the cache (4.1753ms)
✔ put, read and remove round-trip (6.7835ms)
✔ an unchanged result skips the disk; a changed one does not (6.0862ms)
✔ nothing is remembered about nothing, and the last real answer survives it (6.7872ms)
✔ a write that failed leaves the key writable, not silenced (3.0678ms)
✔ liveOnly refuses the remembered copy, and only while it runs (2.7428ms)
✔ liveOnly holds until the outermost call is done, and hands back its answer (2.4201ms)
✔ signing out empties the cache — and the guard that skips writes with it (2.6023ms)
✔ a different signer empties the device first; the same one keeps their work (2.7331ms)
✔ an unclaimed device whose remembered identity is this person keeps its cache (3.0406ms)
✔ a clear that fails leaves the device the last owner's, and says so out loud (2.4517ms)
✔ an unreadable owner record refuses the claim and clears nothing (7.9088ms)
✔ a device nobody has claimed is emptied on the next sign-in (2.4027ms)
✔ subscribers are told the state at once and on every change (2.0446ms)
✔ a network failure is queueable; a real answer from the server is not (31.1591ms)
✔ the browser knowing it has no signal makes any failure a connectivity one (3.4666ms)
✔ the outbox replays in the order the work was done, not the order it comes off disk (18.6349ms)
✔ a checkpoint written mid-replay is what the retry starts from (4.3298ms)
✔ a permanent failure keeps the item with its reason, and the rest still go (13.6366ms)
✔ a lost signal stops the flush and leaves everything exactly as it was (4.0045ms)
✔ a refusal the server actually gave is a reason even with the radio down (5.3079ms)
✔ an item this build has no handler for says so instead of blinking forever (3.346ms)
✔ one technician's outbox is invisible to the next person on the tablet (6.4119ms)
✔ an item queued before anyone signed in belongs to whoever is here (4.5032ms)
✔ with nobody signed in, a technician's queued work stays out of sight (4.4117ms)
✔ the badge hears the current list at once, and again on every change (93.2589ms)
✔ attachAutoFlush replays at once and again on every `online` (37.7043ms)
✔ a flagged failure is a lost connection even with the radio showing bars (4.206ms)
✔ a caller that joins a running flush is told so, and onSynced fires once per drain (45.0508ms)
✔ the overwrite note is keyed by ticket and dated when it can be (63.5834ms)
✔ keyset paging walks every row of a multi-page read (9.734ms)
✔ keyset paging keeps every surviving row when one is deleted mid-walk (8.9897ms)
✔ offset paging reads every page of a still source, in order (2.5215ms)
✔ offset paging reads every row when the source caps pages below the constant (1.6492ms)
✔ a source that gives no total is taken at its first page (2.3036ms)
✔ offset paging skips a row when one is deleted mid-walk (3.3855ms)
✔ keyset paging stops rather than spinning when the key never advances (1.3989ms)
✔ keyset paging walks every row when the source caps pages below the constant (1.1438ms)
✔ keyset paging ends when the rows run out (0.6191ms)
✔ quarters run backwards from the current one, on calendar boundaries (8.0926ms)
✔ years are calendar years, newest first (2.6073ms)
✔ a work date knows its quarter (0.7095ms)
✔ chased in the last three days counts as chased (1.5665ms)
✔ a recovery landing is caught during import, before anything subscribes (9.4611ms)
✔ an ordinary landing is not a recovery (5.407ms)
✔ the word without the token is not a recovery, and is stripped (9.786ms)
✔ a real recovery landing is left in the address bar for supabase-js (3.496ms)
✔ the event arriving after import wakes every subscriber (2.4459ms)
✔ unsubscribing stops the callback (2.5846ms)
✔ a landing already caught by the hash does not fire again (3.2584ms)
✔ an ordinary start has nothing to say (6.45ms)
✔ an expired link says so, and says what to do (2.9242ms)
✔ expiry is recognised from the description as well as the code (7.6863ms)
✔ any other complaint is passed on in Auth's own words, once (6.463ms)
✔ clear() puts it back, and a later reset is caught again (4.0761ms)
✔ a plain section is its own address, both ways (10.608ms)
✔ every section in the menu round-trips (1.1175ms)
✔ a job is named in the address and comes back whole (0.8409ms)
✔ a job number is escaped, because job numbers are freeform (0.7611ms)
✔ the screens that hang off a job carry it with them (0.6728ms)
✔ a contextual screen with no job has no address at all (3.6841ms)
✔ a contextual screen cannot be asked for on its own (0.708ms)
✔ Auth's own hashes are not routes (0.6481ms)
✔ nothing, nonsense and a broken escape are all no route (6.4671ms)
✔ a cold load can open a job, and stops there (2.6852ms)
✔ a plain section lands as itself, and nothing lands as nothing (0.8596ms)
✔ a job and its own screens share one history entry (0.5689ms)
✔ a save that lands quickly keeps the screen's own word (2.4183ms)
✔ a wait past the threshold says what is happening and where the work goes (0.6714ms)
✔ a time that is not a number is the start of the wait, not the worry (0.3887ms)
✔ only a flat false means the device knows it is offline (2.2334ms)
✔ the strip names the record, the addresses and the time in Grande Prairie's clock (73.3406ms)
✔ a queued row past its time is due; a failed one says so and carries its error (3.6802ms)
✔ a reminder row names its text and its time, and no addresses (6.3866ms)
(node:33696) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/scheduledSends.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the kinds are the three sends and a reminder (4.616ms)
✔ a local time becomes the instant, on either side of the clock change (80.2602ms)
✔ a time already passed, or more than ninety days away, is refused in words (4.5048ms)
✔ the time is said in Grande Prairie's clock (2.0607ms)
✔ the fire-time gate refuses a locked account or one that lost the tab (2.1607ms)
✔ the fire-time gate is the send function's own, on the record as it stands now (1.7426ms)
✔ a row claimed and silent for fifteen minutes is stuck; a queued one never is (1.295ms)
✔ the label names the record the way Job detail does (1.6057ms)
✔ the words name the record, the job, every address and the time (7.3911ms)
✔ moving a send says what moves — the time, the addresses, or both (9.4214ms)
✔ the push the scheduler's devices get names the result, the record and the job, and points at the job (1.5275ms)
✔ a reminder's push is the reminder itself, on the job's page or the app's (0.4201ms)
✔ a reminder's text is one line of a few to three hundred characters, and its words name the time and the job (4.5225ms)
✔ items start in list order (13.7008ms)
✔ no more than `concurrency` sends are ever in flight (88.5164ms)
✔ a single worker really is one at a time (61.138ms)
✔ starts are paced by minInterval even with instant sends (2.2654ms)
✔ a rate-limit refusal is waited out and retried, not counted failed (2.0304ms)
✔ an unavailable transport is retried too (0.7261ms)
✔ Retry-After on the error beats the doubling backoff (0.9253ms)
✔ a retryable failure gives up after three retries (1.388ms)
✔ anything else is not retried — a bad address is not a busy server (0.7653ms)
✔ one failure does not strand the rest of the run (1.0254ms)
✔ Stop starts nothing new and lets what is in flight finish (35.2839ms)
✔ Stop during a backoff abandons the retry (1.7635ms)
✔ Stop is answered part-way through a long wait, not at the end of it (1.1304ms)
✔ a Retry-After of an hour is capped, not obeyed (2.7986ms)
✔ progress is reported once per settled item, in order (1.6284ms)
✔ an empty list is a no-op, not a hang (0.4031ms)
✔ isTransientSendError knows what is worth waiting for (0.3735ms)
✔ retryAfterFromError reads the property or the message, else nothing (0.328ms)
✔ backoff doubles from a second (0.2484ms)
(node:23628) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/hoursDose.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
(node:23628) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
✔ Ask hours includes all 1,001 rows with an API cap of 250 (72.9583ms)
✔ Ask hours includes all 1,001 rows with an API cap of 1000 (3.9484ms)
✔ a complete read shorter than the budgets is not called partial (2.4441ms)
✔ a server cap that does not divide the budget stops ON it, never past it (85.4115ms)
✔ a server handing back one row at a time stops on the request budget, not on rows (88.5398ms)
✔ exactly the row budget is reported partial, which is the safe way to be wrong (35.4181ms)
✔ the partial note names the period and says the slice is not chronological (45.4196ms)
✔ a reduced server cap still respects the backup part's row budget (3.9971ms)
✔ backup reads 0 rows completely with an API cap of 250 (2.8889ms)
✔ backup reads 1000 rows completely with an API cap of 250 (7.7054ms)
✔ backup reads 1001 rows completely with an API cap of 250 (4.394ms)
✔ backup reads 0 rows completely with an API cap of 1000 (0.3487ms)
✔ backup reads 1000 rows completely with an API cap of 1000 (2.4376ms)
✔ backup reads 1001 rows completely with an API cap of 1000 (5.4499ms)
✔ signs in normally when everything answers (6.1641ms)
✔ a getSession() that never settles does not hang the app (60.3765ms)
✔ a profile read that never settles does not hang the app (60.6906ms)
✔ a network failure never signs the user out (1.3758ms)
✔ offline with nothing remembered lands on sign-in, not a spinner (60.3167ms)
✔ an account the server says has no access is still signed out (1.6046ms)
✔ no session at all, while online, shows sign-in (0.8958ms)
✔ an expired token that could not refresh offline restores from cache (1.0772ms)
✔ no session while the browser knows it is offline restores from cache (1.0485ms)
✔ a deliberate sign-out still lands on sign-in, even with no network (1.5ms)
✔ an unreadable identity is reported as unreadable, not as nobody (54.4636ms)
✔ an identity that is simply absent is not called unreadable (61.3065ms)
✔ identityFrom refuses an account with no tabs (0.7686ms)
✔ a plain filename passes through untouched (2.7395ms)
✔ accents fold to their plain letters, not dashes (0.5253ms)
✔ emoji and other non-ASCII become a single dash (0.5168ms)
✔ the URL-hazard characters go: # ? % (0.4231ms)
✔ dots survive mid-name so extensions stay real (0.4679ms)
✔ leading and trailing junk is trimmed (0.3563ms)
✔ a name with nothing usable falls back (0.4571ms)
✔ length is capped at a hundred characters (0.3889ms)
✔ rows roll up into the four tiles and the whole outstanding position (16.5596ms)
✔ money adds in cents, so a run of awkward figures lands exactly (0.8269ms)
✔ null totals stay null — a role without prices never sees $0.00 (0.7951ms)
✔ a bucket with nothing in it is zero and null, not missing (1.0143ms)
✔ clients come back biggest first (0.9142ms)
✔ with no prices to sort by, the busiest client leads and ties go by name (39.4947ms)
✔ two clients with the same name stay two rows; a job with no client is its own (0.7031ms)
✔ a bucket name this build doesn't know is left out of both the tiles and the total (0.4089ms)
✔ only a missing routine reads as missing — a refusal is a refusal (1.0127ms)
(node:17456) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/ticketCheck.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the ceilings are data.js's, word for word (4.2875ms)
✔ a clean draft has nothing to say (1.2729ms)
✔ each gap is its own phrase (1.3276ms)
✔ a ticket with everything wrong lists it all, in the editor's order (2.5578ms)
✔ an empty ticket has a fingerprint, and it is always the same one (2.9079ms)
✔ the order lines and crew come back in is not an edit (1.0179ms)
✔ a changed quantity is a different ticket (0.6067ms)
✔ a changed rate, label, crew figure or delay note all move it (0.8444ms)
✔ the same figures typed and read back are the same fingerprint (0.5599ms)
✔ dropping a line changes it, and so does adding one (0.428ms)
✔ nothing is called an overwrite without both fingerprints (0.4512ms)
✔ an untouched ticket is not an overwrite; somebody else's save is (0.3664ms)
✔ the retry that finds its own copy on the row says nothing (0.7465ms)
✔ labels match the card exactly or by their plain words, welds and services apart (5.3194ms)
✔ what the card lacks is named, and bad quantities are skipped (2.29ms)
✔ a save reaches every subscriber (8.528ms)
✔ unsubscribing stops delivery (0.4946ms)
✔ the same message twice in quick succession is announced once (0.4179ms)
✔ different messages are not deduped against each other (0.3805ms)
✔ an empty message is not announced (0.3377ms)
✔ muting silences saves, and unmuting restores them (0.486ms)
✔ mute is counted, so nesting cannot unmute early (0.5502ms)
✔ an unbalanced unmute cannot drive the counter negative (0.326ms)
✔ a tone is carried through to the subscriber (0.6541ms)
✔ tone defaults to ok (0.6168ms)
✔ a toast carrying an action is never deduped: the same removal twice is two Undos (0.4758ms)
✔ clearAction takes down an action toast and leaves a plain one alone (0.468ms)
✔ a ticket copy keyed by a job is a job, keyed by a ticket is a ticket (7.5023ms)
✔ an assessment copy is always its job's, whatever the suffix looks like (0.5836ms)
✔ keys that are not recovery copies are not rows (0.404ms)
✔ a key built from a job with no id is not offered as a job to open (0.319ms)
✔ a ticket id is never mistaken for a job id (0.4613ms)
✔ each job is looked up once however many copies name it (0.7422ms)
✔ rows name the job through the job record, newest copy first (0.8546ms)
✔ a copy keyed by a reopened draft takes its job from the drafts already on screen (0.4651ms)
✔ a copy nothing can name is still listed, under what is known of it (0.6259ms)
✔ an undated copy sorts last rather than to the top (0.5312ms)
✔ when it was kept reads as today, yesterday, or a date (46.0638ms)
✔ every inline script block is named by the hash of its text as the parser reads it (24.3817ms)
✔ index.html's one inline script is the theme, and it is hashed rather than let through wholesale (11.502ms)
✔ the app's policy allows what the screens load and nothing looser (1.6932ms)
✔ every CDN script and hand-called API in the screens is a host the policy allows (6.57ms)
✔ the approval page and the error page load nothing from anywhere (4.8344ms)
✔ secured() sends the always-on headers and lets a route tighten one (52.2357ms)
✔ the Worker sets the policy on every document, and the approval page has no inline handler (2.5346ms)
✔ an empty archive is still a valid archive (8.041ms)
✔ the central directory is where the trailer says it is (2.1176ms)
✔ every entry is announced and described once (1.4479ms)
✔ each central header points at its own local header (1.4556ms)
✔ sizes are stored, not compressed (1.233ms)
✔ names are flagged as UTF-8 so accents survive (0.9815ms)
✔ the CRC is a real CRC-32 (0.834ms)
✔ an entry may bring its own CRC, and it is the one that is written (1.1802ms)
✔ binary content survives byte for byte (4.4942ms)
✔ safeFilename removes what a filesystem refuses (1.1277ms)
✔ safeFilename keeps ordinary names intact (0.4105ms)
✔ safeFilename collapses whitespace and strips trailing dots (0.1892ms)
✔ safeFilename never returns nothing (0.3209ms)
ℹ tests 768
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 768
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 3326.5171
