✔ the half cent rounds up, not down — $0.70 at 5% is $0.04 (3.086ms)
✔ the cents agree with data.js gstOn at every whole cent under $5,000 (1231.877ms)
✔ an exempt client is charged nothing, and the total is the subtotal (1.9481ms)
✔ a rate the row does not carry is the ordinary 5%, never exempt (0.2326ms)
✔ a client rate that is neither camel nor snake case is still read (0.2417ms)
✔ null money is three blank cells, not a row of zeros (0.1905ms)
✔ commas, quotes and newlines in a label reach the CSV helper unaltered (0.5047ms)
✔ the ticket export carries the invoice number and the day it was invoiced (0.2052ms)
✔ a database with no invoice_number column says so instead of leaving a silent blank (0.2855ms)
✔ a client id the row does not carry is blank, never invented (0.233ms)
✔ lines come out in the export's ticket order, each ticket's own order kept (0.2388ms)
✔ a line's total is quantity times rate, rounded the way the invoice rounds it (0.166ms)
✔ a ticket with no lines is left out of the line export and counted out of it (0.1628ms)
✔ the line export says in the file that it carries no GST (0.1095ms)
✔ an empty export is still a file with its caption and columns (0.0845ms)
✔ clearSessionState is declared above the recheck effect that captures it (1.3689ms)
✔ every early return in App comes after the last hook call (1.098ms)
✔ runs every item in order, one at a time (5.5626ms)
✔ one failure does not strand the rest, and is carried back with its error (1.1784ms)
✔ Stop finishes the one in hand and starts no more (0.6836ms)
✔ Stop before the first one starts nothing (0.2962ms)
✔ an empty list is a run that did nothing, not an error (0.4059ms)
✔ onStart names who is being worked on, before the work (1.1905ms)
✔ a person with no name still reads as a person (0.754ms)
✔ the summary of a clean run is just the count (0.3704ms)
✔ the summary names failures rather than counting them (1.0883ms)
✔ a stopped run says how many were never started (0.8097ms)
✔ a long list of failures counts the tail instead of running off the line (0.6019ms)
✔ the total defaults to everything the run knows about (0.2849ms)
(node:31584) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ jobs file under their client and the month they were raised (4.3541ms)
✔ the month comes from the local clock, and falls back sanely (0.6666ms)
✔ a second file of the same name in one folder is numbered (0.4763ms)
✔ csv cells are quoted and never formulas (0.463ms)
✔ the zip is named for what it holds (0.4269ms)
✔ an archived ticket keeps the rate it was billed at, and the summary agrees with the invoice (36.4603ms)
✔ a ticket filed before the snapshot existed still reads the client's rate (0.3067ms)
✔ the job text file carries the record, the money and the crew (9.3735ms)
✔ the downloaded zip checks out when it is the one that was built (2.8141ms)
✔ a byte changed inside a file is caught (3.0512ms)
✔ a zip past what its trailer can count is refused, never written short (1087.781ms)
✔ the drift check sees a swap that leaves every count the same (0.3241ms)
✔ a file left out of the download is caught, and so is one that isn't from this build (0.7648ms)
✔ a complete build says so and holds every job's paperwork (2.3188ms)
✔ a read the network could not answer is a gap in the archive, not an empty job (45.4382ms)
✔ anything served from this device's memory during a build is flagged too (0.8951ms)
✔ a ticket read that fails is a gap, not the end of the build (0.9984ms)
✔ an invoice that would not render is a named gap, and the ticket is still archived (0.8418ms)
✔ a report PDF that would not download is a named gap too (0.8827ms)
✔ the build records what each job held, for the clear to check against (0.7939ms)
✔ a job that has gained work since the build stops the clear (0.1319ms)
✔ a minted duplicate name never collides with a file really called that (0.1287ms)
✔ mapLimit runs a few at a time and answers in order (74.5223ms)
✔ something that isn't a zip is said to be so (0.2546ms)
(node:6104) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askDrafts.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ pickTemplate reads the kind of work out of the words (2.2307ms)
✔ a job draft needs the project and the LSD, and says which is missing (2.6877ms)
✔ a job draft is the dialog's seed and one sentence (1.6189ms)
✔ a ticket draft cleans its lines and date (5.5803ms)
✔ a JHA draft keeps only real hazards and string site fields (2.1143ms)
✔ csv: every cell quoted, formulas made text, a BOM in front, columns first (2.9682ms)
✔ html: scripts, handlers and javascript: urls go; the page stays (1.4743ms)
✔ sizes read as bytes, KB or MB (0.3079ms)
✔ a workbook is one worksheet per sheet with the columns as the first row (1.8426ms)
✔ a pdf writes the title, the sections and their tables down the page and over page breaks (1.3667ms)
(node:34036) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askFiles.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the name keeps the person's words, drops what a filesystem refuses, and takes the kind's extension (3.7368ms)
✔ html and css are text, bounded (1.6381ms)
✔ csv is one table, every row as wide as the columns, cells kept as strings or numbers (1.2931ms)
✔ xlsx is one to ten sheets, names made safe and unique, rows counted across sheets (4.6029ms)
✔ pdf is a titled document of sections, each with something in it (0.9927ms)
✔ the words name the file and what is in it, and the size is a rough count (0.9371ms)
(node:11316) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askKnowledge.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ Ask knows every screen in TABS by its key and label, and no other (4.6413ms)
✔ the knowledge block names every screen and stays a page, not a manual (1.2521ms)
✔ the context is checked and cut to size, never trusted (0.7681ms)
✔ the where line names the screen, the job and the ticket, and wraps the help as data (0.616ms)
(node:31056) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askLearn.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the extractor is told to keep how the app works and nothing about records or people (3.4733ms)
✔ the answer is read strictly: JSON or nothing, bounded, deduplicated, replaces only notes that exist (2.6538ms)
✔ the cap holds: room for new notes is what is left under MAX_LEARNED (0.325ms)
✔ the notes enter the prompt graded by the speaker's role now, wrapped as data; none means nothing (0.5874ms)
✔ forgetting is worded from the note, shortened when long (0.4599ms)
(node:20768) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askLoop.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ windowTurns keeps the last 24, clips long turns and ends on the question (4.5554ms)
✔ a plain answer comes straight back, with the key in the header and no tools sent when none are offered (45.9789ms)
✔ a tool call is run, its answer sent back as records, and the trace says so (2.2355ms)
✔ a read that fails is handed back as an error result and the loop goes on (2.9597ms)
✔ past the call limit the model is asked to answer with no tool allowed (5.5096ms)
✔ past the time budget the next request allows no tool either (1.1221ms)
✔ the API's refusals become plain words and never carry the key (1.5114ms)
✔ an answer with no words still says something (0.5974ms)
✔ the system prompt names the person, the day in Grande Prairie and the rules (35.7219ms)
✔ wrapRecords says what the records are and that they are data (0.713ms)
(node:33776) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askSends.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ a name resolves to the one contact on file, exact first, then by containment (3.2763ms)
✔ unknown, ambiguous and no-email names refuse, naming the person (1.1063ms)
✔ a bare address passes only when the person typed it, case-insensitively (1.1688ms)
✔ addresses are deduped and capped at the transport's limit (0.6439ms)
✔ the JHA gate is send-jha's: a PDF, and the signer or a sending role (1.9947ms)
✔ the ticket gate is send-ticket-approval's: unsigned, something on it, own or the office (0.8583ms)
✔ a ticket approval goes to the ticket's contact, else the job's rep, else refuses (0.5908ms)
✔ the words name the file, the job and every address, and say again when it is (0.7637ms)
✔ an answer keeps what was learned, and the × drops one note from the turn alone (4.532ms)
✔ a proposal the card confirms in place is told from a draft by its kind, and the button says what it does (0.6018ms)
✔ an action rides the answer turn for the card, never the send, and Not now drops it (0.6532ms)
✔ foldTranscripts takes segments in order and cumulative repeats once (0.6476ms)
✔ dictation rebuilds the box from what was typed plus what was said (0.4771ms)
✔ a thread is turns in order, trace kept beside the answer and not sent (0.3213ms)
✔ only the last ASK_KEEP turns are kept (0.3449ms)
✔ jobLinks marks real job numbers by membership, never by pattern (0.7702ms)
(node:25236) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/askTools.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ every tool sits behind a tab the app has (2.6429ms)
✔ toolsFor offers exactly the tools behind the tabs held, and the price roles for a ticket (2.1009ms)
✔ the lists and the JHA send sit behind job; the ticket send behind ticket and a price role (0.9247ms)
✔ the timer tools sit behind job, and the kinds are scheduledSends.ts's (0.5474ms)
✔ the definitions carry only what the API takes (0.6505ms)
✔ the templates and hazard names are data.js's, word for word (0.3177ms)
✔ searchArgs cleans what the model sends (0.6518ms)
✔ a trace line says what was read or drafted, in words (0.3348ms)
✔ make_file is for anyone holding a tab, never an account with none, and its kinds are askFiles.ts's (7.8208ms)
✔ the six helpers sit behind their screens, and the equipment filters are the screen's own (2.5674ms)
✔ the five more sit behind their screens and roles (0.87ms)
(node:31512) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/emailIn.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
(node:31512) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
✔ the address rule is the same code on the screens and in the function (3.6494ms)
✔ the chase plan is the same code on the tracker and in the function (5.6385ms)
✔ the card's words name the due tickets and who is left alone and why; nothing due is a refusal (1.7071ms)
✔ Home's attention questions are the same code on the board and in the function (4.9544ms)
✔ an ordinary morning says nothing (4.5195ms)
✔ nothing read at all is nothing to say, not a crash (0.3022ms)
✔ a failed backup names the failure but keeps the raw error off the board (0.949ms)
✔ a failed restore is not called a backup (0.3501ms)
✔ a failed file check is not called a backup either (0.3493ms)
✔ a run that finished is not news (0.349ms)
✔ a lapsed drive connection is the first thing said (0.3847ms)
✔ a due date well in the past means nothing is picking the schedule up (0.3363ms)
✔ a backup a little late is not late enough to say (0.2754ms)
✔ a drive that was never connected has no schedule to be late for (0.3506ms)
✔ background errors inside the day are counted and grouped by function (0.7153ms)
✔ errors older than the day are left out, and one error is singular (0.304ms)
✔ a row stamped a minute ahead of this device's clock still counts (0.2045ms)
✔ agoPhrase reads like a person saying it (0.3295ms)
✔ the signature is steady for one state and empty when there is nothing to say (1.2418ms)
✔ a new error, or one more of them, moves the signature (0.6012ms)
✔ a dismissed strip stays down until its signature changes (0.3826ms)
✔ nothing to say is never suppressed, and nothing is written for a non-signature (0.2767ms)
✔ a failed file check does not send the office to a button that is not there (0.2904ms)
✔ clearing a dismissal forgets the signature, so the same trouble returning is news again (0.2406ms)
✔ the digest's kind words are the strip's, read back from the function (1.2165ms)
(node:13292) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/backupRun.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ only buckets whose keys are never reused are carried over (3.4309ms)
✔ an object is carried over when the base holds its name at the same size (0.5391ms)
✔ a rewritable bucket is never carried over, even on a perfect match (0.4052ms)
✔ the base is the newest stamped folder that is not this run's own (0.5424ms)
✔ the cursor remembers the base it chose, and that it looked (0.7084ms)
✔ a paused page and a finished page both carry the reused count (0.5577ms)
✔ the panel says how many were carried over, and nothing when none were (0.3462ms)
✔ a copy with no recorded hash is not carried over — it is read through and hashed (0.3631ms)
✔ the redirect URI is the stored app address plus the provider (2.531ms)
✔ only the origin of the stored address counts — a path or a trailing slash is dropped (0.3389ms)
✔ with no address stored, this window's origin is the honest guess (1.6015ms)
✔ a stored address that isn't a URL falls back rather than throwing (0.3341ms)
✔ the three providers, and each with a name a person would recognise (1.5345ms)
✔ a blank secret box leaves the stored secret alone — the column is not in the patch at all (1.0991ms)
✔ a typed secret is written, trimmed (0.3604ms)
✔ whitespace alone is still blank — it does not erase a stored secret (0.3457ms)
✔ client IDs are trimmed, and an emptied box does clear the column (0.7281ms)
✔ the schedule is clamped to what the database's own checks allow (0.5135ms)
✔ nonsense in the number boxes lands on the defaults rather than on NaN (0.3265ms)
✔ the sentence under the keep box says the number the save would write (0.2882ms)
✔ one kept backup is “the most recent one”, not “the 1 most recents” (0.2172ms)
✔ the four frequencies the schedule knows all survive (0.2304ms)
✔ the next run is only worked out once there is a drive to run to (1.196ms)
✔ the patch names the one row and stamps it (0.2189ms)
✔ the patch never carries a refresh token, an account or a provider — those are the callback's (0.214ms)
✔ a connected callback is read, and the query it came home with is taken off (0.3016ms)
✔ a refusal carries the function's own words (0.1906ms)
✔ a cancelled consent screen is not an error (0.1119ms)
✔ anything else on the address bar is left where it was (0.1708ms)
✔ no backup query at all means there is nothing to say (0.1589ms)
✔ an outcome word we don't know is treated as a failure, not as success (0.1379ms)
✔ the reason a connection failed survives the reload that follows it (1.2014ms)
✔ a refresh of the backup state does not rewrite the schedule boxes (0.8192ms)
✔ a before-restore copy is recognised by the same prefix the server writes (0.6349ms)
✔ the restore is confirmed by the backup's own name, character for character (0.2742ms)
✔ a failed backup says the schedule carries it; a failed restore says where the app is (0.3934ms)
✔ a restore-all that failed after the wipe names both ways out (0.2134ms)
✔ a restore-all that failed before the wipe says nothing has been changed (0.1951ms)
✔ a per-job restore that failed touched nothing else (0.1495ms)
✔ a Google client id pasted with the console's helper text is reduced to the id (0.3715ms)
✔ a run's figures come out of counts, and a run with none reads as zero (0.3821ms)
✔ one run is not a trend (0.4825ms)
✔ the line runs oldest to newest and is scaled from zero, so half is half (0.3899ms)
✔ a backup that halved says so; one that held steady does not (0.3461ms)
✔ only runs that wrote a copy are plotted (0.3173ms)
✔ a file check reads as one sentence, and says when there was nothing to repair (0.568ms)
✔ the panel lists only the notes the file check's sentence has not already said (1.0086ms)
(node:8012) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/backupRestore.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the phases run safety, wipe, accounts, tables, files, activity (6.3405ms)
✔ a fresh cursor starts at safety and remembers who is driving (0.5331ms)
✔ a cursor read back out of jsonb is filled in rather than trusted (1.4023ms)
✔ the counts always carry skipped and collisions, at zero if nothing else (0.526ms)
✔ the counts carry the safety copy's name, because a failed restore is read from them (1.5505ms)
✔ a retry reuses the last attempt's safety copy rather than copying the damage (2.5143ms)
✔ the reused copy is named on the run, and the panel reads that list (10.9389ms)
✔ the wipe deletes in batches, and remembers the size and what it took (1.2751ms)
✔ a batch the cap cancels is halved, and only the floor is a failure (0.973ms)
✔ only a statement timeout is answered by trying again with less (0.6037ms)
✔ the wipe's delete is bounded, and goes through the definer RPC (1.6809ms)
✔ the wipe walks its list once and then hands over to accounts (1.8186ms)
✔ only profiles keeps a row back, and it is the caller's (0.2892ms)
✔ rate_lines is emptied before its history, and the restore says why (0.9406ms)
✔ a part loaded adds to the count; the last one moves to the next table (0.3786ms)
✔ the last table hands over to the files (0.1781ms)
✔ chat history rewinds for its second pass and only then moves on (0.165ms)
✔ a table's parts are its own, and rate_lines never takes the history's (19.594ms)
✔ auth_email comes off before a profile row is written (0.277ms)
✔ a profile row whose account could not be made is left out of the load (0.4035ms)
✔ a row that cannot stand without that person goes; a row that can is blanked (0.4342ms)
✔ a table that never names a profile is not filtered at all (0.2971ms)
✔ a reaction to a message that was left out is left out with it (0.4016ms)
✔ every NOT NULL key into a table the restore can thin is named (0.3104ms)
✔ a part's skipped rows are counted once, however often a slice resumes (0.3094ms)
✔ a deactivated account is re-created but is not invited back in (0.2495ms)
✔ the people left out are named on the run itself (0.318ms)
✔ an account that only missed its email is not written down as an account that was lost (0.4078ms)
✔ the mail failures are marked as they are pushed, not guessed at afterwards (1.9ms)
✔ a restore that raised its safety backup starts it rather than waiting for the cron (0.9334ms)
✔ pass one empties every quote and drops the ids already on the table (0.6625ms)
✔ pass two writes only the quotes, and only where there is one (0.3348ms)
✔ a reply whose quoted message was left out keeps its own words (0.2783ms)
✔ the live Resend and KLIPY keys survive a restore (0.3384ms)
✔ a backup taken before the keys were stripped restores them like any column (0.2869ms)
✔ every column the backup blanks is one the restore skips or never writes (0.3396ms)
✔ the settings row a fresh project has never had is created, not silently skipped (0.3709ms)
✔ a ticket goes back in at zero, because its lines are not there yet (0.5938ms)
✔ only a signed or invoiced ticket gets its own total written back (0.6795ms)
✔ the restore remembers whether it has done the totals (0.3737ms)
✔ only the jobs that had an activity time get one back (0.3905ms)
✔ a report put back is still a PDF (0.2496ms)
✔ the typed name is the backup's own, character for character (0.1973ms)
✔ the refusals say what to do about them (0.2249ms)
✔ rows go back in batches small enough for PostgREST to take (0.0989ms)
✔ the restore keeps the gates it is supposed to keep (1.0534ms)
✔ the three column patches go through the RPC, never an upsert (1.5223ms)
✔ a restore waiting on its safety backup still says it is alive (0.802ms)
✔ an orphaned child is filtered against the rows that actually landed (0.7758ms)
✔ a per-job restore has no safety phase and no wipe (0.2338ms)
✔ the two cursors are told apart by the kind written on them (0.5647ms)
✔ this kind's counts carry the notes themselves, not a tally (0.251ms)
✔ the notes stop before the cursor stops fitting, and say so (0.1982ms)
✔ a part is filtered to the chosen jobs, and children to what landed (0.495ms)
✔ every table a job's records live in is one this filter has an answer for (0.1921ms)
✔ a job already here is left alone, and a number in use is a collision (0.3234ms)
✔ a job that is already here is still a job its missing records go under (0.1407ms)
✔ a run whose chosen jobs are none of them here stops after the jobs table (0.1317ms)
✔ the per-job cursor carries the jobs it found already here (0.2173ms)
✔ a ticket number already in use, or retired, is reported and skipped (0.3652ms)
✔ the same ticket back on the same job is left alone, not called a collision (0.2587ms)
✔ a save key already in use is named, not left to a raw constraint (0.4178ms)
✔ a child row already here is left alone, and said once for the table (0.3949ms)
✔ one of something reads as one of something, in the office's own words (0.3133ms)
✔ a crew row whose person has gone is skipped and counted out loud (0.3969ms)
✔ a name on a row that stands without it is blanked, not dropped (0.248ms)
✔ a client is kept by id, matched by name, or reported lost (0.2814ms)
✔ a contact is matched inside the organisation the job ended up with (0.4726ms)
✔ only the PDFs the restored rows actually point at are fetched (0.3016ms)
✔ the totals and dates are put back only on the rows this run wrote (0.2417ms)
✔ a per-job restore walks part by part and table by table (0.2592ms)
✔ restoring a few jobs deletes nothing and overwrites nothing (1.1541ms)
✔ a restored ticket goes in at zero and is re-priced from its lines (1.5933ms)
✔ a job already in the app is a parent the children still follow (1.4211ms)
✔ a save key already in use is checked for before the batch, not after (1.1567ms)
✔ a damaged file is counted on both cursors and reaches the panel's counts (0.372ms)
✔ a damaged file is left out rather than written over a good one (1.2073ms)
(node:3308) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the zone is the crew's own (7.5291ms)
✔ zonedFields reads Grande Prairie's wall clock, not UTC's (4.2532ms)
✔ zonedFields calls midnight hour 0, never 24 (0.4137ms)
✔ instantAt lands on the wall clock in winter and in summer (0.645ms)
✔ instantAt on the spring-forward morning gives the first real moment (0.7007ms)
✔ instantAt on the fall-back morning takes the first of the two 01:00s (0.323ms)
✔ matchesDay knows each frequency (0.4566ms)
✔ daily rolls to tomorrow once today's hour has gone (0.7898ms)
✔ daily never returns the instant it was asked at (0.4365ms)
✔ weekdays skips Saturday and Sunday (0.7711ms)
✔ weekly waits for its own day (2.7607ms)
✔ weekly asked on its own day before the hour keeps today (0.5103ms)
✔ monthly means the 1st, across a month end and a year end (0.6632ms)
✔ a daily 02:00 still fires on the morning 02:00 does not exist (0.478ms)
✔ a daily 01:00 fires once on the morning 01:00 happens twice (0.3687ms)
✔ rubbish settings fall back to a daily midnight rather than throwing (0.6326ms)
✔ describeSchedule says it in words a person reads (0.3204ms)
✔ the panel's schedule and the function's are the same code (100.1646ms)
(node:31624) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/backupTables.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ every backed-up table is also a loaded table, and the other way round (3.7934ms)
✔ the spec's table list is what is actually backed up (1.0174ms)
✔ parents come before their children in the load order (0.4452ms)
✔ the wipe order is the handover script's own order (2.2131ms)
✔ rate_lines is emptied before its history, because deleting one writes the other (1.6437ms)
✔ everything loaded is wiped first, except the settings row (0.4003ms)
✔ profiles is wiped last, because everything else names it (0.2394ms)
✔ the wipe clears the two log tables the backup does not carry (0.2214ms)
✔ every table has a primary key and a paging answer (0.4557ms)
✔ only the composite-key tables page by offset (0.5305ms)
✔ the buckets are the five the app actually stores in (1.7749ms)
✔ the app_settings column scan finds the columns the migrations added (26.1528ms)
✔ every credential column of app_settings is stripped from a backup (17.111ms)
✔ stripSecrets empties the settings row's credentials and leaves the rest (0.3961ms)
✔ stripSecrets leaves every other table exactly as it found it (0.3966ms)
✔ a restore never writes back the drive connection it is running through (22.9823ms)
✔ the page size is PostgREST's own silent cap (0.2309ms)
✔ chunkRows splits at the cap and never drops or duplicates a row (1.185ms)
✔ part files are flat names, numbered from one, that sort in order (0.3446ms)
✔ a stored object's name survives the round trip through the drive (0.5007ms)
✔ restoring chosen jobs reaches for exactly the tables a job owns (0.1655ms)
✔ a folder is stamped on Grande Prairie's clock (0.7385ms)
✔ a manifest records what went in and says what it holds (1.7908ms)
✔ recordFiles adds up across the slices a run is made of (0.331ms)
✔ the jobs index is what the per-job restore picks from (0.5658ms)
✔ a before-restore copy stops at the manifest and never prunes the drive (0.1682ms)
✔ retention spares the folder a restore is reading from, however old (0.5285ms)
✔ retention keeps the newest N and throws the rest away (0.2297ms)
✔ retention reads the folders in date order however they arrive (0.1355ms)
✔ retention never touches a before-restore folder (0.1821ms)
✔ a backup from a newer schema than the live one is refused (0.1371ms)
✔ the fake drive answers the whole interface (0.9393ms)
✔ the fake drive overwrites a name rather than doubling it, as the real three do (0.3446ms)
✔ deleting a folder takes what is inside it (1.0691ms)
✔ the fake can be told to fail, so retries can be tested (0.6574ms)
✔ Google resumes where the 308 says it got to, not where the sender hoped (58.6188ms)
✔ a 308 with no Range at all is Google saying it took the whole chunk (5.6072ms)
✔ Google asks about the one name it is about to write, not the whole folder (3.2448ms)
✔ an apostrophe in a name does not become a Drive query syntax error (1.4554ms)
✔ Google looks for the folder rather than making a second one of the same name (0.7709ms)
✔ Google creates the folder when the lookup finds none (0.7813ms)
✔ OneDrive resumes where nextExpectedRanges says it got to, not where the sender hoped (1.6533ms)
✔ a 202 with no ranges on it is OneDrive saying it took the whole chunk (1.2241ms)
✔ OneDrive gives up on a session that keeps none of two identical chunks (1.3595ms)
✔ OneDrive creates a folder fail-on-conflict, and looks it up rather than replacing it (1.5665ms)
✔ Dropbox returns the folder it finds rather than asking to create it (0.851ms)
✔ Dropbox creates the folder when the path is free (0.9398ms)
✔ the three providers are asked for exactly the scopes the spec names (0.2292ms)
✔ each authorize URL carries the state, the redirect and offline access (0.7018ms)
✔ an unknown provider is refused rather than guessed at (0.3963ms)
✔ the provider is the last segment of the callback's path, and only if we know it (0.2438ms)
✔ the callback URI is built from the stored app address, origin only (0.3164ms)
✔ the panel and the function build the same string from the same stored address (0.1981ms)
✔ with no app address stored the server refuses rather than guessing (0.3925ms)
✔ credentials come out of the row by provider, and an incomplete pair is refused (0.5906ms)
✔ the three provider lists are one list written three times (0.1183ms)
✔ the callback spends the nonce it was handed and no other (0.7805ms)
✔ a drive's own refusal is retold rather than repeated into the address bar (0.9186ms)
✔ the nonce has to be the one we minted (0.383ms)
✔ the nonce goes stale at ten minutes (0.2264ms)
✔ the shared modules read nothing from the world around them (11.2697ms)
✔ a table part survives being gzipped and read back (50.2488ms)
✔ an empty table still round-trips (3.0686ms)
✔ a slice's budget is spent against its own deadline (0.3912ms)
✔ a heartbeat older than a slice can live is a run to reclaim (0.507ms)
✔ the wipe empties tickets before the list their numbers are burned into (0.4937ms)
✔ the walk of the account list stops on an empty page, not a short one (1.4977ms)
✔ the chain that drives a backup asks for the run it just moved (1.3043ms)
✔ a restore waiting on its safety backup is tended by whichever slice moved the copy (1.0093ms)
✔ a slice that matched no row has lost the run and must stop writing (0.237ms)
✔ a gateway page is named plainly, and anything else keeps its own words (0.5468ms)
✔ every write a slice makes to its own run is conditional on still holding it (1.3362ms)
✔ the kick is held open by the runtime rather than left to be reaped (0.5939ms)
✔ only the flag on a drive's refusal earns a retry (0.4269ms)
✔ the token endpoint gets one more kind of second chance than a drive does (0.256ms)
✔ a passing edge error is transient; a real refusal is not (0.4831ms)
✔ a run is left for reclaim only while it is young enough to still finish (0.1786ms)
✔ a transient edge blip mid-slice leaves the run for the next tick, not failed (0.8049ms)
✔ connectDrive's refresh is under the same three goes as everything else (0.4856ms)
✔ a table that is not finished continues from the key the walk reached (0.4459ms)
✔ the last table hands the run to the files phase (0.1412ms)
✔ an empty table is still a part, so the manifest can say zero (0.1304ms)
✔ the jobs index is folded out of the rows the tables phase reads (0.5615ms)
✔ a bucket is walked depth first and the stack says where it got to (0.4025ms)
✔ a page cut short by the budget resumes where it stopped (0.1872ms)
✔ a cursor read back out of jsonb is filled in rather than trusted (0.5276ms)
✔ the counts the panel shows are the cursor's own (0.2723ms)
✔ a file is hashed the way the index and a restore will compare it (8.765ms)
✔ the file index reads back only records that carry a hash (2.7203ms)
✔ the manifest records how many files are hashed, where, and the spot check (0.3258ms)
✔ a file check's cursor starts empty, revives from jsonb, and its counts read as the panel needs (0.6009ms)
✔ a file check's notes are capped, and the cap says so once (0.3275ms)
✔ the next file check is a whole number of days on, fourteen when the setting is nonsense (0.2934ms)
✔ a file the drive would not hand over is left alone by the check, not re-stored over (0.8465ms)
✔ a run row that could not be made puts the clock back, for both clocks (0.9615ms)
✔ a due time that already has its run is not queued a second one, for both clocks (1.2008ms)
✔ the file rows are reconciled with the folder before the index is written from them (1.2493ms)
✔ crew hours and dose are stored at the precision their columns hold (2.4214ms)
✔ the crew write names the precision of every column it fills (0.8799ms)
✔ the crew boxes and the billing boxes ask for different precision (0.599ms)
✔ ticket writes preserve legacy quantity/rate precision and price the stored values (1.7323ms)
(node:32620) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the app's line arithmetic and the invoice's are the same code (4.6111ms)
✔ a line's charge is what the database would compute, at any scale (1.3528ms)
✔ a rate the rate card no longer offers is still billed at what it was filed at (0.3285ms)
✔ the invoice's subtotal is the sum of its own printed lines (0.8145ms)
✔ GST is a percentage of whole cents, rounded half away from zero (0.429ms)
✔ all three GST call sites answer the same, to the cent (0.7197ms)
✔ a missing GST rate is five percent and never an exemption (0.248ms)
✔ storedNumber rounds the way the column rounds, not the way toFixed does (0.7722ms)
✔ exactRound is half away from zero, and answers zero for what is not a number (0.3724ms)
✔ saving a ticket preserves a line's precision rather than refusing it (2.2998ms)
✔ a ticket with a rep and no history is due, with the address its link goes to (14.179ms)
✔ a rep with a question open is left alone, not chased (1.9938ms)
✔ chased inside the window is skipped; chased outside it is due again (0.5321ms)
✔ a label with no address in it cannot be chased and is counted separately (0.3263ms)
✔ a ticket with no contact at all is a no-email skip, not a crash (0.2926ms)
✔ the reasons are exclusive and tested in order: queried wins over recent and over no email (0.487ms)
✔ recent wins over no email — the ticket is not due either way (0.3505ms)
✔ the due list keeps the order it was read in, because the dialog lists it (0.3204ms)
✔ nothing unsigned means four empty buckets, not a thrown dialog (0.4214ms)
✔ the composer is held whole, per account, and emptied piece by piece (1.4951ms)
✔ a new message is added in order (3.5387ms)
✔ an unchanged refresh returns the same array identity (0.3945ms)
✔ a realtime copy without joins keeps the name it cannot carry (0.2756ms)
✔ the Someone bug: a corrected quote is allowed to land (0.4225ms)
✔ a nameless provisional cannot overwrite a named quote (0.3583ms)
✔ an authoritative null quote clears a deleted parent's text (0.3231ms)
✔ a realtime null quote (no join) keeps the resolved quote (0.3239ms)
✔ null reactions mean unknown; an array is authoritative (0.39ms)
✔ a pin change alone is a change (0.4391ms)
✔ ordering is stable on identical timestamps (0.535ms)
✔ the keys tell apart what matters and ignore order (0.2823ms)
✔ a message deleted inside the page's window leaves the room (0.5728ms)
✔ history older than the page is not the page's to judge (0.2956ms)
✔ a send that landed after the fetch was asked for is kept (0.3067ms)
✔ a stale cached page cannot delete what arrived after it (0.258ms)
✔ an empty page removes nothing (0.2584ms)
(node:34760) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/constantTime.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ secretsMatch answers equality, and an unminted secret matches nothing (3.0125ms)
✔ secretsMatch walks every presented byte and never returns from inside the walk (1.9002ms)
✔ every door compares its secret through secretsMatch, never with an operator (15.596ms)
✔ money always shows two decimals and groups thousands (43.9895ms)
✔ money treats nonsense as zero rather than printing NaN at a client (0.8601ms)
✔ todayLocal is the local day, morning and evening alike (1.6814ms)
✔ todayLocal does not follow UTC over the day boundary (0.7015ms)
✔ todayLocal pads a single-digit month and day (0.3144ms)
✔ contacts is added to any account that has access at all (1.4716ms)
✔ an account already holding contacts does not get it twice (0.3036ms)
✔ no tabs stays no tabs — the universal one never unlocks an empty account (0.2731ms)
✔ tabList hands back a new list rather than editing the profile's (0.3064ms)
✔ the primary is the one that comes back (0.5769ms)
✔ an org id is not enough — the type has to match too (0.2602ms)
✔ with nobody promoted, the first on file stands in (0.2159ms)
✔ nothing to answer with is null, never a stranger (0.1816ms)
✔ a helper is a Helper and everyone else is a Technician (0.1953ms)
✔ an unknown or missing rank falls to Technician, not to nothing (0.1556ms)
✔ prices are an Admin's and a Technician's (0.2127ms)
✔ nobody else sees a price, including nobody at all (0.1268ms)
✔ an approved or invoiced ticket refuses a save outright (0.4754ms)
✔ a Draft save over a ticket sent for signature is refused (0.2539ms)
✔ an ordinary draft save is not refused (0.1618ms)
✔ fileSize names the unit the file is actually in (0.2036ms)
✔ a non-PDF is refused by name, and says what to do (0.4063ms)
✔ a PDF the browser gave no type for is still a PDF (0.2549ms)
✔ an oversized PDF is refused with its own size and the limit (0.1918ms)
✔ no file is not a refusal (0.14ms)
✔ the sanity ceiling is per unit, with a default for anything new (0.1714ms)
✔ a client with no rate on file is billed the ordinary 5% (0.1781ms)
✔ gstOn with no rate given still charges 5% (0.5949ms)
✔ an exempt client is charged nothing, not a rounding of nothing (0.2111ms)
✔ the half-cent rounds up at every rate, so the company is not short (0.1801ms)
✔ a missing rate is charged, never quietly exempted (0.1593ms)
✔ the rate is written so a technician can tell exempt from broken (0.1835ms)
✔ the JHA's standing hazards open unticked (0.1693ms)
✔ ROLE_PRESETS matches tabs_for_role() in the migrations (23.1256ms)
✔ no unapplied handover SQL quietly redefines tabs_for_role (54.2502ms)
✔ a line total rounds the way tickets.total does (0.3577ms)
✔ localDate reads a plain date as local, not UTC (3.632ms)
✔ localDate sits at midday so a DST shift cannot move the day (0.4495ms)
✔ localDate on rubbish gives an invalid date rather than a wrong one (0.4365ms)
✔ ticketDateStamp is MMDD-YY and pads (0.3965ms)
✔ dayMonth is a padded day and a short month, no full stop (31.7567ms)
✔ initialsOf gives letters only, capped at three (0.6579ms)
✔ initialsOf survives names the ticket number would otherwise choke on (0.5326ms)
✔ the 15th is the last day of the first half (1.3972ms)
✔ the 16th starts the second half (0.3246ms)
✔ the second half ends on the real last day of the month (0.512ms)
✔ periods walk backwards without skipping or repeating (0.4408ms)
✔ every period is contiguous with the one before it (0.4502ms)
✔ no period is ever empty or inverted (0.3215ms)
✔ payPeriodLabel reads as a date range with the year once (0.9744ms)
✔ hours always shows two decimals (0.1825ms)
✔ hours treats nonsense as zero rather than NaN on a timesheet (0.1582ms)
✔ ageInDays counts from local midnight, not elapsed hours (0.474ms)
✔ ageInDays is zero for nothing rather than NaN (0.1078ms)
✔ GST is five percent (0.0762ms)
✔ GST rounds a half-cent up, not down (0.6717ms)
✔ GST on ordinary amounts is exact (0.2367ms)
✔ no whole-cent subtotal is ever mis-rounded (270.1993ms)
✔ a sub-cent product rounds to the cent (0.3222ms)
✔ exact products pass through untouched (0.2001ms)
✔ float dust cannot reach a bill (0.1187ms)
✔ nothing times anything is nothing (0.1606ms)
✔ GST on a rounded-line subtotal lands on the cent (0.2665ms)
✔ comma decimals are decimals (0.4116ms)
✔ negatives floor to zero (0.2156ms)
✔ garbage floors to zero (0.2333ms)
(node:14080) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/dayCheck.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ a day with everything filed and sent is done, with nothing missing (2.9914ms)
✔ each gap is its own phrase, filed-but-not-sent apart from not filed (0.6611ms)
✔ no helper on the ticket is a note, not a gap — working alone is a real day (0.3694ms)
✔ the day's furthest-along ticket is the one judged; a sent stamp on a draft counts as sent (0.3704ms)
✔ a kit with nothing in it is the one worth asking about (1.8281ms)
✔ spaces are not a serial (0.3339ms)
✔ one serial is enough to leave the worker alone (0.3438ms)
✔ all three go to the profile, trimmed, blanks included (1.7722ms)
✔ a missing function is recognised by code and by name (0.5769ms)
✔ a refusal, a timeout and a silence are not a missing function (0.3216ms)
✔ a typed serial is news only when the profile does not hold it (0.7699ms)
✔ every screen in TABS has a help entry (3.1044ms)
✔ no help entry names a screen that no longer exists (0.7307ms)
✔ every entry carries a heading and at least one paragraph (0.7053ms)
✔ no entry runs past six paragraphs or two hundred words (0.8831ms)
✔ helpFor answers null for a screen with no entry, so a screen can open with no tip (0.3068ms)
✔ a screen speaks once a run, and the other screens still speak (2.0226ms)
✔ the next run of the app starts the tips over (1.2987ms)
✔ no more tips is the kill switch, this account alone (1.6342ms)
✔ a record that is not the word yes leaves the help where it is (0.3303ms)
✔ no account and no screen mean nothing is owed; a missing run does not (0.2663ms)
(node:29048) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/hoursDose.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ periods refuse nonexistent dates before a database read (4.2447ms)
✔ today is Grande Prairie's date, not UTC's (42.8042ms)
✔ a pay period is the 1st to the 15th or the 16th to the month's end, February included (3.3493ms)
✔ a quarter is the calendar quarter (0.5922ms)
✔ the range is both ends or neither; half a range, a backwards one or more than a year is refused (1.1022ms)
✔ hours sum per job and in total in whole hundredths, days as distinct work dates (1.5189ms)
(node:34472) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ invoice and approval totals retain the stamped rate when the client's rate changes (2.5072ms)
✔ legacy invoices without a snapshot keep their existing fallback behavior (0.3702ms)
✔ the real invoice loader fetches the snapshot before rendering the approved copy (3.0373ms)
✔ approval freezes the rate before sending so the subsequent page cannot change its total (39.7868ms)
✔ a snapshot failure stops the email and token write (1.7856ms)
✔ resending retains an existing exempt rate (2.1782ms)
✔ mail failure does not mark approval sent, but retains the reserved rate for retry (7.2561ms)
✔ an unbroken run of film numbers becomes a range (2.3928ms)
✔ a gap splits the runs instead of being papered over (0.3133ms)
✔ several gaps, several runs (0.2116ms)
✔ a single number stands alone rather than as a range to itself (0.3093ms)
✔ both prefixes, XF first regardless of document order (0.2828ms)
✔ the unhyphenated procedure designation does not count (0.3094ms)
✔ the hyphenated, zero-padded procedure does not count either (0.3387ms)
✔ a number followed by REV is paperwork whatever its padding (0.2078ms)
✔ zero-padded numbers are dropped even without REV after them (0.2047ms)
✔ duplicates collapse and order does not matter (0.538ms)
✔ case survives a sloppy report (0.2195ms)
✔ ultrasonic and the radiographic variants count too (1.9338ms)
✔ the UT procedure pulls the same trick and meets the same guards (0.2364ms)
✔ every prefix reports in paperwork order regardless of page order (0.1571ms)
✔ film numbers in the hundreds, straight off a real report (0.2921ms)
✔ no numbers means an empty answer, not a broken one (0.1847ms)
✔ lookalikes without the word boundary stay out (0.189ms)
✔ fractional quantities stop at thousandths without treating step as an increment (2.4927ms)
✔ money has an explicit two-place limit, including decimal commas (0.6267ms)
✔ an exponent is refused, not swallowed (0.3368ms)
✔ a second decimal point is refused rather than shown (0.3849ms)
✔ a minus sign is refused and never becomes a positive (0.369ms)
✔ a comma decimal is a decimal (0.3526ms)
✔ a grouping comma survives a whole-unit step (0.3834ms)
✔ step decides whether a decimal point is a key at all (0.2819ms)
✔ an emptied box stays empty (0.2906ms)
✔ letters and emoji are refused whole (0.7048ms)
✔ isWholeStep reads the props the callers actually pass (1.094ms)
✔ a decimal comma is a decimal point (1.8126ms)
✔ a comma before three trailing digits is a thousands separator (0.3984ms)
✔ …unless nothing that could be thousands precedes it (0.2814ms)
✔ with both marks present the last one is the decimal point (0.2566ms)
✔ plain numbers pass through untouched (0.2564ms)
✔ nothing, rubbish and negatives floor to zero (0.1804ms)
✔ a read that answers is the answer, and it is remembered (30.4165ms)
✔ with the signal gone, the remembered copy is served — and says so (4.3398ms)
✔ nothing remembered means the failure surfaces (3.7873ms)
✔ a real answer from the server is never replaced by a remembered one (3.1899ms)
✔ a plain failure while the browser knows it is offline still serves the cache (1.7209ms)
✔ put, read and remove round-trip (2.1806ms)
✔ an unchanged result skips the disk; a changed one does not (2.3442ms)
✔ nothing is remembered about nothing, and the last real answer survives it (9.2206ms)
✔ a write that failed leaves the key writable, not silenced (4.8178ms)
✔ liveOnly refuses the remembered copy, and only while it runs (4.1121ms)
✔ liveOnly holds until the outermost call is done, and hands back its answer (2.3052ms)
✔ signing out empties the cache — and the guard that skips writes with it (2.5446ms)
✔ a different signer empties the device first; the same one keeps their work (2.4479ms)
✔ an unclaimed device whose remembered identity is this person keeps its cache (3.873ms)
✔ a clear that fails leaves the device the last owner's, and says so out loud (1.6947ms)
✔ an unreadable owner record refuses the claim and clears nothing (2.7361ms)
✔ a device nobody has claimed is emptied on the next sign-in (1.7032ms)
✔ subscribers are told the state at once and on every change (1.2899ms)
✔ a network failure is queueable; a real answer from the server is not (16.9749ms)
✔ the browser knowing it has no signal makes any failure a connectivity one (2.3349ms)
✔ the outbox replays in the order the work was done, not the order it comes off disk (14.3322ms)
✔ a checkpoint written mid-replay is what the retry starts from (3.9884ms)
✔ a permanent failure keeps the item with its reason, and the rest still go (4.4793ms)
✔ a lost signal stops the flush and leaves everything exactly as it was (2.1918ms)
✔ a refusal the server actually gave is a reason even with the radio down (3.9872ms)
✔ an item this build has no handler for says so instead of blinking forever (2.5393ms)
✔ one technician's outbox is invisible to the next person on the tablet (2.9104ms)
✔ an item queued before anyone signed in belongs to whoever is here (1.503ms)
✔ with nobody signed in, a technician's queued work stays out of sight (2.1591ms)
✔ the badge hears the current list at once, and again on every change (73.3544ms)
✔ attachAutoFlush replays at once and again on every `online` (29.979ms)
✔ a flagged failure is a lost connection even with the radio showing bars (1.0341ms)
✔ a caller that joins a running flush is told so, and onSynced fires once per drain (30.1077ms)
✔ the overwrite note is keyed by ticket and dated when it can be (51.3518ms)
✔ keyset paging walks every row of a multi-page read (9.1434ms)
✔ keyset paging keeps every surviving row when one is deleted mid-walk (4.1569ms)
✔ offset paging reads every page of a still source, in order (1.7275ms)
✔ offset paging reads every row when the source caps pages below the constant (1.1926ms)
✔ a source that gives no total is taken at its first page (1.1292ms)
✔ offset paging skips a row when one is deleted mid-walk (2.244ms)
✔ keyset paging stops rather than spinning when the key never advances (0.8993ms)
✔ keyset paging walks every row when the source caps pages below the constant (0.8912ms)
✔ keyset paging ends when the rows run out (0.4286ms)
✔ quarters run backwards from the current one, on calendar boundaries (5.9854ms)
✔ years are calendar years, newest first (1.5666ms)
✔ a work date knows its quarter (0.3198ms)
✔ chased in the last three days counts as chased (0.6635ms)
✔ a recovery landing is caught during import, before anything subscribes (5.8186ms)
✔ an ordinary landing is not a recovery (3.6145ms)
✔ the word without the token is not a recovery, and is stripped (5.7635ms)
✔ a real recovery landing is left in the address bar for supabase-js (1.8013ms)
✔ the event arriving after import wakes every subscriber (1.9819ms)
✔ unsubscribing stops the callback (2.452ms)
✔ a landing already caught by the hash does not fire again (1.6824ms)
✔ an ordinary start has nothing to say (3.0988ms)
✔ an expired link says so, and says what to do (1.7939ms)
✔ expiry is recognised from the description as well as the code (1.9281ms)
✔ any other complaint is passed on in Auth's own words, once (2.8256ms)
✔ clear() puts it back, and a later reset is caught again (1.5211ms)
✔ a plain section is its own address, both ways (5.3829ms)
✔ every section in the menu round-trips (0.5582ms)
✔ a job is named in the address and comes back whole (0.6249ms)
✔ a job number is escaped, because job numbers are freeform (0.5789ms)
✔ the screens that hang off a job carry it with them (0.4044ms)
✔ a contextual screen with no job has no address at all (0.3337ms)
✔ a contextual screen cannot be asked for on its own (0.4005ms)
✔ Auth's own hashes are not routes (0.2895ms)
✔ nothing, nonsense and a broken escape are all no route (0.5113ms)
✔ a cold load can open a job, and stops there (0.8408ms)
✔ a plain section lands as itself, and nothing lands as nothing (0.6404ms)
✔ a job and its own screens share one history entry (2.2655ms)
✔ a save that lands quickly keeps the screen's own word (1.482ms)
✔ a wait past the threshold says what is happening and where the work goes (0.4727ms)
✔ a time that is not a number is the start of the wait, not the worry (0.2437ms)
✔ only a flat false means the device knows it is offline (1.4039ms)
✔ the strip names the record, the addresses and the time in Grande Prairie's clock (40.8451ms)
✔ a queued row past its time is due; a failed one says so and carries its error (1.7022ms)
✔ a reminder row names its text and its time, and no addresses (2.182ms)
✔ a time the insert policy would refuse is refused here first, in plain words (2.4165ms)
✔ the floor the device keeps is the insert policy's own minute (1.2969ms)
✔ App asks before it cancels, for both the move and the plain schedule (2.0462ms)
(node:28508) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/scheduledSends.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
(node:28508) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
✔ the kinds are the three sends and a reminder (3.0821ms)
✔ a local time becomes the instant, on either side of the clock change (39.6391ms)
✔ a day the month does not have is refused, not rolled into the next one (1.7052ms)
✔ an hour the clock skips is refused; the hour it repeats takes the first (3.1593ms)
✔ what may be proposed is tighter than what the insert policy accepts (1.3807ms)
✔ a time already passed, or more than ninety days away, is refused in words (2.2017ms)
✔ the time is said in Grande Prairie's clock (1.3607ms)
✔ the fire-time gate refuses a locked account or one that lost the tab (1.5019ms)
✔ the fire-time gate is the send function's own, on the record as it stands now (1.2679ms)
✔ a row claimed and silent for fifteen minutes is stuck; a queued one never is (1.1108ms)
✔ the label names the record the way Job detail does (0.6956ms)
✔ the words name the record, the job, every address and the time (2.6709ms)
✔ moving a send says what moves — the time, the addresses, or both (4.2138ms)
✔ the push the scheduler's devices get names the result, the record and the job, and points at the job (1.2952ms)
✔ a reminder's push is the reminder itself, on the job's page or the app's (0.3652ms)
✔ a reminder's text is one line of a few to three hundred characters, and its words name the time and the job (2.408ms)
✔ a status written first time answers nothing to report (0.3969ms)
✔ a status refused once is written again before it is given up on (0.2965ms)
✔ a status refused twice answers the reason and never throws (0.3823ms)
✔ the tick asks what the final write answered, never assuming it landed (0.3797ms)
✔ a send that went and could not be recorded says so, and says not to send it again (0.2794ms)
✔ items start in list order (6.9137ms)
✔ no more than `concurrency` sends are ever in flight (82.9924ms)
✔ a single worker really is one at a time (60.5604ms)
✔ starts are paced by minInterval even with instant sends (0.7975ms)
✔ a rate-limit refusal is waited out and retried, not counted failed (0.8669ms)
✔ an unavailable transport is retried too (0.3342ms)
✔ Retry-After on the error beats the doubling backoff (0.4427ms)
✔ a retryable failure gives up after three retries (0.7394ms)
✔ anything else is not retried — a bad address is not a busy server (0.3334ms)
✔ one failure does not strand the rest of the run (0.4919ms)
✔ Stop starts nothing new and lets what is in flight finish (26.4161ms)
✔ Stop during a backoff abandons the retry (0.683ms)
✔ Stop is answered part-way through a long wait, not at the end of it (0.4439ms)
✔ a Retry-After of an hour is capped, not obeyed (1.5332ms)
✔ progress is reported once per settled item, in order (0.5308ms)
✔ an empty list is a no-op, not a hang (0.2079ms)
✔ isTransientSendError knows what is worth waiting for (0.222ms)
✔ retryAfterFromError reads the property or the message, else nothing (0.1803ms)
✔ backoff doubles from a second (0.1408ms)
(node:2156) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/hoursDose.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
(node:2156) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
✔ Ask hours includes all 1,001 rows with an API cap of 250 (38.2562ms)
✔ Ask hours includes all 1,001 rows with an API cap of 1000 (3.6388ms)
✔ a complete read shorter than the budgets is not called partial (2.1974ms)
✔ a server cap that does not divide the budget stops ON it, never past it (45.755ms)
✔ a server handing back one row at a time stops on the request budget, not on rows (38.46ms)
✔ exactly the row budget is reported partial, which is the safe way to be wrong (19.2103ms)
✔ the partial note names the period and says the slice is not chronological (17.3469ms)
✔ a reduced server cap still respects the backup part's row budget (1.1623ms)
✔ backup reads 0 rows completely with an API cap of 250 (0.907ms)
✔ backup reads 1000 rows completely with an API cap of 250 (2.1114ms)
✔ backup reads 1001 rows completely with an API cap of 250 (1.7716ms)
✔ backup reads 0 rows completely with an API cap of 1000 (0.2152ms)
✔ backup reads 1000 rows completely with an API cap of 1000 (1.1627ms)
✔ backup reads 1001 rows completely with an API cap of 1000 (1.0122ms)
✔ a part out of slice uploads what it read and says it is not exhausted (3.4953ms)
✔ an empty table is exhausted even with the slice already over (0.2262ms)
✔ tiny pages stop at the part's request ceiling rather than spinning (35.9133ms)
✔ the next slice resumes a stopped part from its key (1.6509ms)
✔ signs in normally when everything answers (4.5463ms)
✔ a getSession() that never settles does not hang the app (56.8134ms)
✔ a profile read that never settles does not hang the app (55.2333ms)
✔ a network failure never signs the user out (0.9665ms)
✔ offline with nothing remembered lands on sign-in, not a spinner (61.0321ms)
✔ an account the server says has no access is still signed out (0.7632ms)
✔ no session at all, while online, shows sign-in (0.3711ms)
✔ an expired token that could not refresh offline restores from cache (0.4535ms)
✔ no session while the browser knows it is offline restores from cache (0.4614ms)
✔ a deliberate sign-out still lands on sign-in, even with no network (0.5588ms)
✔ an unreadable identity is reported as unreadable, not as nobody (59.2613ms)
✔ an identity that is simply absent is not called unreadable (62.4825ms)
✔ identityFrom refuses an account with no tabs (0.2966ms)
✔ a plain filename passes through untouched (2.5125ms)
✔ accents fold to their plain letters, not dashes (0.3807ms)
✔ emoji and other non-ASCII become a single dash (0.2723ms)
✔ the URL-hazard characters go: # ? % (0.382ms)
✔ dots survive mid-name so extensions stay real (0.2659ms)
✔ leading and trailing junk is trimmed (0.2197ms)
✔ a name with nothing usable falls back (0.2398ms)
✔ length is capped at a hundred characters (0.2351ms)
✔ rows roll up into the four tiles and the whole outstanding position (4.8653ms)
✔ money adds in cents, so a run of awkward figures lands exactly (0.3732ms)
✔ null totals stay null — a role without prices never sees $0.00 (0.355ms)
✔ a bucket with nothing in it is zero and null, not missing (0.4118ms)
✔ clients come back biggest first (0.4072ms)
✔ with no prices to sort by, the busiest client leads and ties go by name (19.906ms)
✔ two clients with the same name stay two rows; a job with no client is its own (0.5745ms)
✔ a bucket name this build doesn't know is left out of both the tiles and the total (0.4031ms)
✔ only a missing routine reads as missing — a refusal is a refusal (0.7783ms)
(node:33100) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/ticketCheck.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the ceilings are data.js's, word for word (1.9235ms)
✔ a clean draft has nothing to say (0.7533ms)
✔ each gap is its own phrase (0.7192ms)
✔ a ticket with everything wrong lists it all, in the editor's order (0.2974ms)
✔ an empty ticket has a fingerprint, and it is always the same one (1.9873ms)
✔ the order lines and crew come back in is not an edit (0.8853ms)
✔ a changed quantity is a different ticket (0.3666ms)
✔ a changed rate, label, crew figure or delay note all move it (0.5149ms)
✔ the same figures typed and read back are the same fingerprint (0.3506ms)
✔ dropping a line changes it, and so does adding one (0.2468ms)
✔ nothing is called an overwrite without both fingerprints (0.2535ms)
✔ an untouched ticket is not an overwrite; somebody else's save is (0.2003ms)
✔ the retry that finds its own copy on the row says nothing (0.5453ms)
✔ labels match the card exactly or by their plain words, welds and services apart (3.2733ms)
✔ what the card lacks is named, and bad quantities are skipped (0.5516ms)
✔ a save reaches every subscriber (4.1421ms)
✔ unsubscribing stops delivery (0.3485ms)
✔ the same message twice in quick succession is announced once (0.264ms)
✔ different messages are not deduped against each other (0.288ms)
✔ an empty message is not announced (0.2573ms)
✔ muting silences saves, and unmuting restores them (0.324ms)
✔ mute is counted, so nesting cannot unmute early (0.4177ms)
✔ an unbalanced unmute cannot drive the counter negative (0.276ms)
✔ a tone is carried through to the subscriber (0.3987ms)
✔ tone defaults to ok (0.3874ms)
✔ a toast carrying an action is never deduped: the same removal twice is two Undos (0.296ms)
✔ clearAction takes down an action toast and leaves a plain one alone (0.2709ms)
✔ a ticket copy keyed by a job is a job, keyed by a ticket is a ticket (3.3853ms)
✔ an assessment copy is always its job's, whatever the suffix looks like (0.2664ms)
✔ keys that are not recovery copies are not rows (0.5245ms)
✔ a key built from a job with no id is not offered as a job to open (0.2402ms)
✔ a ticket id is never mistaken for a job id (0.3537ms)
✔ each job is looked up once however many copies name it (0.403ms)
✔ rows name the job through the job record, newest copy first (0.5039ms)
✔ a copy keyed by a reopened draft takes its job from the drafts already on screen (0.3135ms)
✔ a copy nothing can name is still listed, under what is known of it (0.4512ms)
✔ an undated copy sorts last rather than to the top (0.4684ms)
✔ when it was kept reads as today, yesterday, or a date (31.7213ms)
✔ every inline script block is named by the hash of its text as the parser reads it (11.9643ms)
✔ index.html's one inline script is the theme, and it is hashed rather than let through wholesale (3.6699ms)
✔ the app's policy allows what the screens load and nothing looser (0.815ms)
✔ every CDN script and hand-called API in the screens is a host the policy allows (3.2154ms)
✔ the approval page and the error page load nothing from anywhere (2.0598ms)
✔ secured() sends the always-on headers and lets a route tighten one (38.5529ms)
✔ the Worker sets the policy on every document, and the approval page has no inline handler (1.5417ms)
✔ an empty archive is still a valid archive (5.1531ms)
✔ the central directory is where the trailer says it is (0.9425ms)
✔ every entry is announced and described once (0.5432ms)
✔ each central header points at its own local header (0.5425ms)
✔ sizes are stored, not compressed (0.3963ms)
✔ names are flagged as UTF-8 so accents survive (0.4342ms)
✔ the CRC is a real CRC-32 (0.3589ms)
✔ an entry may bring its own CRC, and it is the one that is written (0.4815ms)
✔ binary content survives byte for byte (2.2273ms)
✔ safeFilename removes what a filesystem refuses (0.6324ms)
✔ safeFilename keeps ordinary names intact (0.2623ms)
✔ safeFilename collapses whitespace and strips trailing dots (0.1475ms)
✔ safeFilename never returns nothing (0.1054ms)
ℹ tests 783
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 783
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 1756.6591
