(node:33924) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/scheduledSends.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
(node:33924) ExperimentalWarning: stripTypeScriptTypes is an experimental feature and might change at any time
✔ control: unauthorized ticks cannot claim or deliver (2.5501ms)
✔ control: losing the queued claim cannot deliver (2.495ms)
✔ control: successful delivery records sent (0.9078ms)
✔ control: failed delivery records failed (0.6585ms)
✔ defect: failed sent-status write still reports success and leaves sending (1.9338ms)
✔ defect: failed failure-status write also leaves sending with an ok response (0.6875ms)
✔ defect: nonexistent calendar date silently becomes December 1 (34.5479ms)
✔ defect: nonexistent spring-forward time silently becomes 01:30 (1.0684ms)
✔ defect: proposed time passes application guard but violates SQL insertion window (1.0514ms)
✔ control: real fire branch delivers jha once (1.2184ms)
✔ control: real fire branch refuses locked scheduler for jha (1.019ms)
✔ control: real fire branch delivers report once (0.2298ms)
✔ control: real fire branch refuses locked scheduler for report (0.228ms)
✔ control: real fire branch delivers ticket_approval once (0.3197ms)
✔ control: real fire branch refuses locked scheduler for ticket_approval (0.1682ms)
✔ control: real fire branch delivers reminder once (0.385ms)
✔ control: real fire branch refuses locked scheduler for reminder (0.1827ms)
✔ control: deleted jha is not delivered (0.2396ms)
✔ control: deleted report is not delivered (0.2143ms)
✔ control: deleted ticket_approval is not delivered (0.1516ms)
✔ control: reminders fail explicitly without devices or accepted pushes (0.2796ms)
✔ control: already approved tickets are refused and resends stamp the chase (0.3991ms)
✔ the strip names the record, the addresses and the time in Grande Prairie's clock (35.9039ms)
✔ a queued row past its time is due; a failed one says so and carries its error (1.6754ms)
✔ a reminder row names its text and its time, and no addresses (1.4566ms)
(node:7936) [MODULE_TYPELESS_PACKAGE_JSON] Warning: Module type of file:///C:/Users/troll/OneDrive/Documents/Work/NDE%20web%20app%20design/claudex-work/37dbe6165f/supabase/functions/_shared/scheduledSends.ts is not specified and it doesn't parse as CommonJS.
Reparsing as ES module because module syntax was detected. This incurs a performance overhead.
To eliminate this warning, add "type": "module" to \\?\C:\Users\troll\OneDrive\Documents\Work\NDE web app design\claudex-work\37dbe6165f\package.json.
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ the kinds are the three sends and a reminder (2.7763ms)
✔ a local time becomes the instant, on either side of the clock change (35.3899ms)
✔ a time already passed, or more than ninety days away, is refused in words (2.0178ms)
✔ the time is said in Grande Prairie's clock (1.4362ms)
✔ the fire-time gate refuses a locked account or one that lost the tab (1.1927ms)
✔ the fire-time gate is the send function's own, on the record as it stands now (0.7089ms)
✔ a row claimed and silent for fifteen minutes is stuck; a queued one never is (0.7172ms)
✔ the label names the record the way Job detail does (0.5234ms)
✔ the words name the record, the job, every address and the time (1.9133ms)
✔ moving a send says what moves — the time, the addresses, or both (3.0386ms)
✔ the push the scheduler's devices get names the result, the record and the job, and points at the job (1.0012ms)
✔ a reminder's push is the reminder itself, on the job's page or the app's (0.305ms)
✔ a reminder's text is one line of a few to three hundred characters, and its words name the time and the job (1.7639ms)
ℹ tests 38
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 38
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 364.4381
